<Namespace Name="System.Windows.Forms">
  <Metadata><Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="de3d7b337699f794b1d27959727821d8e228cf48" /><Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="434f60616a9793fa8436744549fc856e94f7a648" /><Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="HT" /><Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="ko-KR" /><Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="08/24/2018" /><Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="30737227" /></Metadata><Docs>
    <summary><span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-101"><see cref="N:System.Windows.Forms" /> 네임스페이스에는 Microsoft Windows 운영 체제의 풍부한 사용자 인터페이스 기능을 활용하는 Windows 기반 응용 프로그램을 만들 수 있는 클래스가 포함되어 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-101">The <see cref="N:System.Windows.Forms" /> namespace contains classes for creating Windows-based applications that take full advantage of the rich user interface features available in the Microsoft Windows operating system.</span></span></summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-102">다음 표에서의 클래스를 보여 줍니다. <xref:System.Windows.Forms> 네임 스페이스 범주로 그룹화 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-102">The following table shows the classes in <xref:System.Windows.Forms> namespace grouped into categories.</span></span>  
  
|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-103">범주 클래스</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-103">Class category</span></span>|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-104">설명</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-104">Details</span></span>|  
|--------------------|-------------|  
|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-105">사용자 정의 컨트롤 및 폼 컨트롤</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-105">-   Control, User Control, and Form</span></span>|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-106">내에서 대부분의 클래스는 <xref:System.Windows.Forms> 네임 스페이스에서 파생 된 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.Control> 클래스입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-106">Most classes within the <xref:System.Windows.Forms> namespace derive from the <xref:System.Windows.Forms.Control> class.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-107">합니다 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.Control> 에 표시 되는 모든 컨트롤에 대 한 기본 기능을 제공 하는 클래스는 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.Form>합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-107">The <xref:System.Windows.Forms.Control> class provides the base functionality for all controls that are displayed on a <xref:System.Windows.Forms.Form>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-108"><xref:System.Windows.Forms.Form> 클래스는 응용 프로그램 내에서 창을 나타냅니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-108">The <xref:System.Windows.Forms.Form> class represents a window within an application.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-109">이 대화 상자, 모덜리스 windows 및 인터페이스 MDI (다중 문서) 클라이언트 및 부모 창을 포함합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-109">This includes dialog boxes, modeless windows, and Multiple Document Interface (MDI) client and parent windows.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-110">파생 하 여 사용자 지정 컨트롤을 만들 수도 있습니다는 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.UserControl> 클래스입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-110">You can also create your own controls by deriving from the <xref:System.Windows.Forms.UserControl> class.</span></span>|  
|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-111">-메뉴 및 도구 모음</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-111">-   Menus and Toolbars</span></span>|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-112">Windows Forms에는 다양 한 최신 모양 및 동작 (모양 및 느낌)을 사용 하 여 사용자 고유의 사용자 지정 툴바와 메뉴를 만드는 클래스 집합을 포함 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-112">Windows Forms contains a rich set of classes for creating your own custom toolbars and menus with modern appearance and behavior (look and feel).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-113"><xref:System.Windows.Forms.ToolStrip>를 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.MenuStrip>, <xref:System.Windows.Forms.ContextMenuStrip>, 및 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.StatusStrip> 각각 도구 모음, 메뉴 모음, 상황에 맞는 메뉴 및 상태 표시줄을 만드는 데 사용할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-113"><xref:System.Windows.Forms.ToolStrip>, <xref:System.Windows.Forms.MenuStrip>, <xref:System.Windows.Forms.ContextMenuStrip>, and <xref:System.Windows.Forms.StatusStrip> can be used to create toolbars, menu bars, context menus, and status bars, respectively.</span></span>|  
|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-114">-컨트롤</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-114">-   Controls</span></span>|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-115"><xref:System.Windows.Forms> 네임 스페이스는 다양 한 기능이 풍부한 사용자 인터페이스를 만드는 데 사용할 수 있는 컨트롤 클래스를 제공 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-115">The <xref:System.Windows.Forms> namespace provides a variety of control classes that you can use to create rich user interfaces.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-116">일부 컨트롤은 같은 애플리케이션에서 데이터 항목에 대 한 설계 되었습니다 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.TextBox> 고 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.ComboBox> 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-116">Some controls are designed for data entry within the application, such as <xref:System.Windows.Forms.TextBox> and <xref:System.Windows.Forms.ComboBox> controls.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-117">다른 컨트롤 등의 애플리케이션 데이터를 표시 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.Label> 고 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.ListView>입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-117">Other controls display application data, such as <xref:System.Windows.Forms.Label> and <xref:System.Windows.Forms.ListView>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-118">또한 네임 스페이스와 같은 애플리케이션 내에서 명령을 호출 하는 것에 대 한 컨트롤을 제공 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.Button>합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-118">The namespace also provides controls for invoking commands within the application, such as <xref:System.Windows.Forms.Button>.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-119">합니다 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.WebBrowser> 컨트롤 및 HTML 클래스와 같은 관리 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.HtmlDocument>, 표시 하 고 관리 되는 Windows Forms 애플리케이션 내에서 HTML 페이지를 조작 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-119">The <xref:System.Windows.Forms.WebBrowser> control and managed HTML classes, such as <xref:System.Windows.Forms.HtmlDocument>, let you display and manipulate HTML pages within your managed Windows Forms application.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-120"><xref:System.Windows.Forms.MaskedTextBox> 컨트롤은 자동으로 마스크를 정의할 수 있는 고급 데이터 항목 컨트롤을 받거나 사용자 입력을 거부 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-120">The <xref:System.Windows.Forms.MaskedTextBox> control is an advanced data entry control that lets you define masks that automatically accept or reject user input.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-121">또한 사용할 수 있습니다는 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.PropertyGrid> 컨트롤의 디자이너에 게 표시 되는 속성을 표시 하는 사용자 고유의 Windows Forms 디자이너를 만들 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-121">Additionally, you can use the <xref:System.Windows.Forms.PropertyGrid> control to create your own Windows Forms Designer that displays the designer-visible properties of the controls.</span></span>|  
|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-122">레이아웃</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-122">-   Layout</span></span>|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-123">예: 양식 화면에서 컨트롤의 레이아웃을 제어 하거나 컨트롤 도움을 Windows Forms의 몇 가지 중요 한 클래스.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-123">Several important classes in Windows Forms help control the layout of controls on a display surface, such as a form or control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-124"><xref:System.Windows.Forms.FlowLayoutPanel> 직렬 방식으로 포함 된 모든 컨트롤을 배치 하 고 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.TableLayoutPanel> 셀 및 행으로 고정된 된 표 컨트롤에 대 한을 정의할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-124"><xref:System.Windows.Forms.FlowLayoutPanel> lays out all the controls it contains in a serial manner, and <xref:System.Windows.Forms.TableLayoutPanel> lets you define cells and rows for laying out controls in a fixed grid.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-125"><xref:System.Windows.Forms.SplitContainer> 표시 화면에 두 개 이상 조정 가능한 부분으로 나눕니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-125"><xref:System.Windows.Forms.SplitContainer> divides your display surface into two or more adjustable parts.</span></span>|  
|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-126">데이터 및 데이터 바인딩</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-126">-   Data and Data Binding</span></span>|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-127">Windows Forms 데이터 바인딩 데이터베이스 및 XML 파일과 같은 원본에 대 한 다양 한 아키텍처를 정의 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-127">Windows Forms defines a rich architecture for binding to data sources such as databases and XML files.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-128"><xref:System.Windows.Forms.DataGridView> 컨트롤 데이터를 표시 하기 위해 사용자 지정할 수 있는 테이블을 제공 하 고 셀, 행, 열 및 테두리를 사용자 지정할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-128">The <xref:System.Windows.Forms.DataGridView> control provides a customizable table for displaying data, and lets you customize cells, rows, columns, and borders.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-129"><xref:System.Windows.Forms.BindingNavigator> 컨트롤은 이동 하 고 폼에서 데이터로 작업 하는 표준화 된 방법을 나타냅니다. <xref:System.Windows.Forms.BindingNavigator> 자주 이룹니다는 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.BindingSource> 컨트롤을 폼에 데이터 레코드를 탐색 하 고 상호 작용 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-129">The <xref:System.Windows.Forms.BindingNavigator> control represents a standardized way to navigate and work with data on a form; <xref:System.Windows.Forms.BindingNavigator> is frequently paired with the <xref:System.Windows.Forms.BindingSource> control to move through data records on a form and interact with them.</span></span>|  
|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-130">-구성 요소</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-130">-   Components</span></span>|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-131">컨트롤 외에 <xref:System.Windows.Forms> 네임 스페이스에서 파생 되지 않은 다른 클래스를 제공 합니다 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.Control> 클래스 하지만 여전히 Windows 기반 애플리케이션에 시각적 기능을 제공 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-131">Besides controls, the <xref:System.Windows.Forms> namespace provides other classes that do not derive from the <xref:System.Windows.Forms.Control> class but still provide visual features to a Windows-based application.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-132">와 같은 일부 클래스 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.ToolTip> 고 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.ErrorProvider>, 기능을 확장 또는 사용자에 게 정보를 제공 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-132">Some classes, such as <xref:System.Windows.Forms.ToolTip> and <xref:System.Windows.Forms.ErrorProvider>, extend the capabilities or provide information to the user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-133">사용 하 여는 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.Help> 고 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.HelpProvider> 클래스를 애플리케이션의 사용자에 게 도움말 정보를 표시할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-133">With the <xref:System.Windows.Forms.Help> and <xref:System.Windows.Forms.HelpProvider> classes, you can display Help information to a user of your applications.</span></span>|  
|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-134">-일반 대화 상자</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-134">-   Common Dialog Boxes</span></span>|<span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-135">Windows 열기 및 파일을 저장, 글꼴 또는 텍스트 색, 조작 또는 인쇄 등의 작업을 수행할 때 일관 된 사용자 인터페이스를 제공 하는 데 사용할 수 있는 몇 가지 일반적인 대화 상자를 제공 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-135">Windows provides several common dialog boxes that you can use to give your application a consistent user interface when performing tasks such as opening and saving files, manipulating the font or text color, or printing.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-136">합니다 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.OpenFileDialog> 및 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.SaveFileDialog> 클래스 찾아을 열거나 저장할 파일의 이름을 입력 하 여 사용자 수 있는 대화 상자를 표시 하는 기능을 제공 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-136">The <xref:System.Windows.Forms.OpenFileDialog> and <xref:System.Windows.Forms.SaveFileDialog> classes provide the functionality to display a dialog box that lets the user locate and enter the name of a file to open or save.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-137">합니다 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.FontDialog> 클래스의 요소를 변경 하려면 대화 상자를 표시 합니다 <xref:System.Drawing.Font> 애플리케이션에서 사용 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-137">The <xref:System.Windows.Forms.FontDialog> class displays a dialog box to change elements of the <xref:System.Drawing.Font> used by your application.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-138">합니다 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.PageSetupDialog>, <xref:System.Windows.Forms.PrintPreviewDialog>, 및 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.PrintDialog> 클래스 사용자가 문서를 인쇄의 여러 측면을 제어할 수 있는 대화 상자를 표시 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-138">The <xref:System.Windows.Forms.PageSetupDialog>, <xref:System.Windows.Forms.PrintPreviewDialog>, and <xref:System.Windows.Forms.PrintDialog> classes display dialog boxes that enable the user to control aspects of printing documents.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-139">Windows 기반 애플리케이션에서 인쇄 하는 방법에 대 한 자세한 내용은 참조는 <xref:System.Drawing.Printing> 네임 스페이스입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-139">For more information about printing from a Windows-based application, see the <xref:System.Drawing.Printing> namespace.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-140">일반 대화 상자, 외에 <xref:System.Windows.Forms> 네임 스페이스를 제공는 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.MessageBox> 표시 하 고 사용자 로부터 데이터를 검색할 수 있는 메시지 상자를 표시 하기 위한 클래스입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-140">Besides the common dialog boxes, the <xref:System.Windows.Forms> namespace provides the <xref:System.Windows.Forms.MessageBox> class for displaying a message box that can display and retrieve data from the user.</span></span>|  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-141">내에서 여러 클래스를 가지는 <xref:System.Windows.Forms> 이전 요약에 설명 된 클래스에 대 한 지원을 제공 하는 네임 스페이스입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-141">There are several classes within the <xref:System.Windows.Forms> namespace that provide support to the classes mentioned in the previous summary.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-142">지원 클래스의 예로 열거형, 이벤트 인수 클래스 및 컨트롤 및 구성 요소 내에서 이벤트가 사용 되는 대리자를 들 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-142">Examples of the supporting classes are enumerations, event argument classes, and delegates used by events within controls and components.</span></span>  
  
> [!CAUTION]
>  <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-143">Windows Forms 네임 스페이스 내의 클래스는 Windows 서비스 내에서 지원 되지 않습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-143">Classes within the Windows Forms namespace are not supported for use within a Windows service.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-144">서비스에서 이러한 클래스를 사용 하는 동안 저하 서비스 성능 및 런타임 예외와 같은 예기치 않은 문제가 발생할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-144">Trying to use these classes from within a service may produce unexpected problems, such as diminished service performance and run-time exceptions.</span></span>  
>   
>  <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-145">.NET Framework 버전 1.1 사용 하는 경우.NET Framework 1.0을 설정 해야 합니다 Windows XP 비주얼 스타일을 지 원하는 Windows Forms 애플리케이션 설정 했는지 확인 합니다 `FlatStyle` 속성을 컨트롤의 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.FlatStyle.System?displayProperty=nameWithType> 인 매니페스트를 포함 하 고 프로그램 실행 파일입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-145">If you are using .NET Framework version 1.1 or .NET Framework 1.0 and you must make your Windows Forms application support Windows XP visual styles, make sure that you set the `FlatStyle` property of your controls to <xref:System.Windows.Forms.FlatStyle.System?displayProperty=nameWithType> and include a manifest with your executable file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-146">매니페스트는 실행 파일과 동일한 디렉터리에 있는 별도 파일 또는 애플리케이션 실행 파일 내에 리소스로 포함 된 XML 파일.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-146">A manifest is an XML file that is included either as a resource within your application executable file or as a separate file that resides in the same directory as the executable file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-147">매니페스트의 예에 대 한 예제 섹션을 참조 합니다 <xref:System.Windows.Forms.FlatStyle> 열거형입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-147">For an example of a manifest, see the Example section for the <xref:System.Windows.Forms.FlatStyle> enumeration.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-148">Windows XP에서 사용할 수 있는 비주얼 스타일을 사용 하는 방법에 대 한 자세한 내용은 "를 사용 하 여 Windows XP 시각적 스타일에서 the 사용자 인터페이스 디자인 및 개발" MSDN 라이브러리의을 참조 하세요.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-148">For more information about how to use the visual styles available in Windows XP, see "Using Windows XP Visual Styles in the User Interface Design and Development" in the MSDN Library.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="ac1dd-149">기본적으로.NET Framework 버전 1.1, 1.2 및 2.0에 대 한 비주얼 스타일을 사용 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="ac1dd-149">By default visual styles are enabled for the .NET Framework versions 1.1, 1.2, and 2.0.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
  </Docs>
</Namespace>