<Namespace Name="System.Runtime.Remoting.Channels">
  <Metadata>
    <Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="a8760d09a78e9a2fbe294d04c88c1e7efe895792" />
    <Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96" />
    <Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="HT" />
    <Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="ko-KR" />
    <Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="05/10/2018" />
    <Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="30735467" />
  </Metadata>
  <Docs>
    <summary>
      <span data-ttu-id="07ddd-101">
        <see cref="N:System.Runtime.Remoting.Channels" /> 네임스페이스에는 클라이언트가 원격 개체의 메서드를 호출할 때 전송 매체로 사용되는 채널 및 채널 싱크를 지원하고 처리하는 클래스가 포함되어 있습니다.</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="07ddd-101">The <see cref="N:System.Runtime.Remoting.Channels" /> namespace contains classes that support and handle channels and channel sinks, which are used as the transport medium when a client calls a method on a remote object.</span>
      </span>
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="07ddd-102">채널은 응용 프로그램 도메인, 프로세스 또는 컴퓨터와 같은 원격 경계를 가로질러 응용 프로그램 간에 메시지를 전송하는 개체입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="07ddd-102">Channels are objects that transport messages between applications across remoting boundaries, whether between application domains, processes, or computers.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="07ddd-103">채널은 인바운드 메시지를 끝점에서 수신하고 아웃바운드 메시지를 다른 끝점으로 보낼 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="07ddd-103">A channel can listen on an endpoint for inbound messages, send outbound messages to another endpoint, or both.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="07ddd-104">그러면 채널의 다른 쪽 끝에 공용 언어 런타임이 없어도 광범위한 프로토콜을 연결할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="07ddd-104">This enables you to plug in a wide range of protocols, even if the common language runtime is not at the other end of the channel.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="07ddd-105">채널을 보내기 전에 또는 메시지를 받은 후에 채널 싱크 개체의 체인에 따라 각 개체를 보냅니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="07ddd-105">Channels send each object along a chain of channel sink objects prior to sending or after receiving a message.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="07ddd-106">이 싱크 체인 전송 또는 스택 작성기 싱크 등의 기본 채널 기능에 필요한 싱크가 포함 하지만 메시지 또는 스트림을 특별 한 작업을 수행 하는 채널 싱크 체인을 사용자 지정할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="07ddd-106">This sink chain contains sinks required for basic channel functionality, such as transport or stack builder sinks, but you can customize the channel sink chain to perform special tasks with a message or a stream.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="07ddd-107">각 체인의 각 싱크는 개체를 수신 하 고 특정 작업을 수행 하면 체인의 다음 싱크로 전달 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="07ddd-107">Each sink in each chain receives the object, performs a specific operation, and passes it on to the next sink in the chain.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="07ddd-108">이 자주 사용 됩니다 하는 경우 메시지 싱크를 통해 받은 개체는 다음 싱크로 전달 해야 하는 규칙이 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="07ddd-108">There is no rule that the exact object received by a message sink must be passed on to the next sink, though this will often be the case.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="07ddd-109">자세한 내용은 참조 [채널](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6e9b60e0-9bc0-47b4-a8ef-3b78585f9a18) 및 [싱크 및 싱크 체인](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/516aaab7-5b3d-4c72-83dd-d435c01af8f6)합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="07ddd-109">For more information, see [Channels](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6e9b60e0-9bc0-47b4-a8ef-3b78585f9a18) and [Sinks and Sink Chains](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/516aaab7-5b3d-4c72-83dd-d435c01af8f6).</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
  </Docs>
</Namespace>