<Namespace Name="System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection">
  <Metadata>
    <Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="b482f98a5c4316a191cd9beb8d2d226874520920" />
    <Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="434f60616a9793fa8436744549fc856e94f7a648" />
    <Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="HT" />
    <Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="ko-KR" />
    <Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="08/24/2018" />
    <Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="30735497" />
  </Metadata>
  <Docs>
    <summary>
      <span data-ttu-id="7559f-101">
        <see cref="N:System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection" /> 네임스페이스는 응용 프로그램에 대해 확장된 보호를 사용하는 인증을 지원합니다.</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="7559f-101">The <see cref="N:System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection" /> namespace provides support for authentication using extended protection for applications.</span>
      </span>
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="7559f-102">설계 통합 Windows 인증 (IWA)의 일부 자격 증명 시도 응답이 유니버설이 다시 사용 되거나 전달 수 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7559f-102">The design of Integrated Windows Authentication (IWA) allows for some credential challenge responses to be universal, meaning they can be re-used or forwarded.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7559f-103">이 특정 디자인 기능이 필요 하지 않은 경우 다음 응답 해야 하는 챌린지를 사용 하 여 생성, 최소한 대상 관련 정보를 기껏해야 일부 채널 관련 정보입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7559f-103">If this particular design feature is not needed then the challenge responses should be constructed with, at minimum, target specific information and, at best, also some channel specific information.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7559f-104">그런 다음 서비스가 수 있도록 자격 증명 시도 응답 서비스 (서비스 공급자 이름 또는 SPN) 관련 정보가 포함, 필요한 경우 특정 채널 확장 된 보호 제공 정보 (채널 바인딩 토큰 또는 CBT).</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7559f-104">Services can then provide extended protection to ensure that credential challenge responses contain service specific information (a Service Provider Name or SPN) and, if necessary, channel specific information (a channel binding token or CBT).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7559f-105">서비스 자격 증명 교환에이 정보를 사용 하 여 얻은 수 부적절 하 게 자격 증명 시도 응답의 악의적인 사용 으로부터 더 잘 보호할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7559f-105">With this information in the credential exchanges, services are able to better protect against malicious use of credential challenge responses that might have been improperly obtained.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
    <altmember cref="T:System.Net.TransportContext" />
    <altmember cref="N:System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection.Configuration" />
  </Docs>
</Namespace>