<Namespace Name="System.DirectoryServices">
  <Metadata>
    <Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="adffd4946d205352de973348aed1e2b3523733ce" />
    <Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="434f60616a9793fa8436744549fc856e94f7a648" />
    <Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="HT" />
    <Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="ko-KR" />
    <Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="08/24/2018" />
    <Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="30734627" />
  </Metadata>
  <Docs>
    <summary>
      <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-101">
        <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" /> 네임스페이스를 사용하면 관리 코드에서 Active Directory 도메인 서비스에 쉽게 액세스할 수 있습니다.</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="0be1e-101">The <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" /> namespace provides easy access to Active Directory Domain Services from managed code.</span>
      </span>
      <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-102">이 네임스페이스에는 ADSI(Active Directory Services Interfaces) 기술을 사용하는 두 개의 구성 요소 클래스인 <see cref="T:System.DirectoryServices.DirectoryEntry" />와 <see cref="T:System.DirectoryServices.DirectorySearcher" />가 들어 있습니다.</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="0be1e-102">The namespace contains two component classes, <see cref="T:System.DirectoryServices.DirectoryEntry" /> and <see cref="T:System.DirectoryServices.DirectorySearcher" />, which use the Active Directory Services Interfaces (ADSI) technology.</span>
      </span>
      <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-103">ADSI는 다양한 네트워크 공급자에 대해 작업할 수 있도록 Microsoft에서 유연성 있는 도구로 제공하는 인터페이스 집합입니다.</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="0be1e-103">ADSI is the set of interfaces that Microsoft provides as a flexible tool for working with a variety of network providers.</span>
      </span>
      <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-104">관리자는 ADSI를 통해 네트워크 규모에 관계없이 네트워크 상의 리소스를 비교적 쉽게 찾아서 관리할 수 있습니다.</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="0be1e-104">ADSI gives the administrator the ability to locate and manage resources on a network with relative ease, regardless of the size of the network.</span>
      </span>
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-105">Active Directory Domain Services 서비스 공급자 중 하나를 사용 하 여이 네임 스페이스의 클래스를 사용할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-105">The classes in this namespace can be used with any of the Active Directory Domain Services service providers.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-106">현재 공급자: 인터넷 정보 서비스 (IIS), LDAP Lightweight Directory Access Protocol (), Novell NetWare NDS Directory Service (), 및 WinNT 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-106">The current providers are: Internet Information Services (IIS), Lightweight Directory Access Protocol (LDAP), Novell NetWare Directory Service (NDS), and WinNT.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-107">ADSI는 Microsoft Active Directory Domain Services의 응용 프로그램을 단일 인터페이스를 사용 하 여 네트워크에서 다양 한 디렉터리와 상호 작용할 수 있게 해 주는 프로그래밍 방식 인터페이스입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-107">ADSI is a programmatic interface for Microsoft Active Directory Domain Services that enables your applications to interact with diverse directories on a network using a single interface.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-108">ADSI를 사용 하 여 데이터베이스 백업, 프린터, 액세스 및 사용자 계정 관리와 같은 일반적인 작업을 수행 하는 응용 프로그램을 만들 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-108">Using ADSI, you can create applications that perform common tasks, such as backing up databases, accessing printers, and administering user accounts.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-109">이러한 클래스를 사용 하기 전에 Active Directory Domain Services에 대 한 기본적인 지식이 있다고 가정 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-109">It is assumed that you have a general understanding of Active Directory Domain Services before using these classes.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-110">Active Directory Domain Services에 대 한 자세한 내용은 항목을 참조 하세요. [Active Directory 개체 소개](http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=121193&clcid=0x409) 하 고 [Active Directory 기술 배경](http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=121194&clcid=0x409)에서 다음 항목 뿐만 아니라 MSDN library [ http://msdn.microsoft.com/library ](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library):</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-110">For more information on Active Directory Domain Services, see the topics [Introduction to Active Directory Objects](http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=121193&clcid=0x409) and [Active Directory Technology Backgrounder](http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=121194&clcid=0x409), as well as the following topics in the MSDN library at [http://msdn.microsoft.com/library](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library):</span></span>  
  
-   [<span data-ttu-id="0be1e-111">Active Directory Domain Services를 사용 하 여</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-111">Using Active Directory Domain Services</span></span>](http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=121195&clcid=0x409)  
  
-   [<span data-ttu-id="0be1e-112">Active Directory 서비스 인터페이스</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-112">Active Directory Service Interfaces</span></span>](http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=121197&clcid=0x409)  
  
-   [<span data-ttu-id="0be1e-113">Lightweight Directory Access Protocol</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-113">Lightweight Directory Access Protocol</span></span>](http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=121198&clcid=0x409)  
  
-   [<span data-ttu-id="0be1e-114">공급자 인터페이스를 구현 하는 Active Directory 서비스</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-114">Implementing Active Directory Service Interfaces Providers</span></span>](http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=121199&clcid=0x409)  
  
-   [<span data-ttu-id="0be1e-115">ADSI 개체에 바인딩</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-115">Binding to an ADSI Object</span></span>](http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=121200&clcid=0x409)  
  
-   [<span data-ttu-id="0be1e-116">IADsOpenDSObject::OpenDSObject</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-116">IADsOpenDSObject::OpenDSObject</span></span>](http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=121201&clcid=0x409)  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-117">Active Directory 도메인 서비스 트리 구조를 사용합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-117">Active Directory Domain Services use a tree structure.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-118">트리의 각 노드 속성 집합을 포함합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-118">Each node in the tree contains a set of properties.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-119">이 네임 스페이스를 사용 하 여 트래버스, 검색, 트리를 수정 하 고 읽기 및 쓰기 노드의 속성.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-119">Use this namespace to traverse, search, and modify the tree, and read and write to the properties of a node.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-120"><xref:System.DirectoryServices.DirectoryEntry> 클래스는 Active Directory 도메인 서비스 계층 구조의 노드나 개체를 캡슐화합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-120">The <xref:System.DirectoryServices.DirectoryEntry> class encapsulates a node or object in the Active Directory Domain Services hierarchy.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-121">개체에 바인딩 속성을 읽고 특성 업데이트에 대 한이 클래스를 사용 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-121">Use this class for binding to objects, reading properties, and updating attributes.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-122">도우미 클래스와 함께 <xref:System.DirectoryServices.DirectoryEntry> 지원 수명 주기에 대 한 만들기, 삭제, 이름 바꾸기, 자식 노드를 이동 및 자식을 열거를 포함 한 관리 및 탐색 메서드를 제공 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-122">Together with helper classes, <xref:System.DirectoryServices.DirectoryEntry> provides support for life-cycle management and navigation methods, including creating, deleting, renaming, moving a child node, and enumerating children.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-123">사용 된 <xref:System.DirectoryServices.DirectorySearcher> Active Directory Domain Services 계층에 대 한 쿼리를 수행 하는 클래스입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-123">Use the <xref:System.DirectoryServices.DirectorySearcher> class to perform queries against the Active Directory Domain Services hierarchy.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-124">LDAP는 검색을 지 원하는 시스템 제공의 유일한 서비스 인터페이스 ADSI (Active Directory) 공급자입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-124">LDAP is the only system-supplied Active Directory Service Interfaces (ADSI) provider that supports searching.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-125">Active Directory Domain Services 계층 구조에서 검색 <xref:System.DirectoryServices.DirectorySearcher> 의 인스턴스를 반환 <xref:System.DirectoryServices.SearchResult>에 인스턴스에 포함 된를 <xref:System.DirectoryServices.SearchResultCollection> 클래스.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-125">A search of the Active Directory Domain Services hierarchy through <xref:System.DirectoryServices.DirectorySearcher> returns instances of <xref:System.DirectoryServices.SearchResult>, which are contained in an instance of the <xref:System.DirectoryServices.SearchResultCollection> class.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-126">참고: 대부분의 클래스, 메서드 및 속성에는 <xref:System.DirectoryServices> 네임 스페이스 사용을 <xref:System.Security.Permissions.SecurityAction.LinkDemand> 코드 액세스 보안 옵션입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-126">Note: Many of the classes, methods, and properties in the <xref:System.DirectoryServices> namespace use the <xref:System.Security.Permissions.SecurityAction.LinkDemand> code access security option.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-127">즉, 코드 액세스 보안 요청이-just-in-time 컴파일 중 발생 하 고 수요를 호출 하는 어셈블리 및 전체 호출 스택 위로 없습니다만 수행 되도록 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-127">This means that the code access security demand only occurs during just-in-time compilation and that the demand is performed only on the calling assembly and not up the entire call stack.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="0be1e-128">이 인해 호출자는 신뢰할 수 없는 코드에 런타임 시이 네임 스페이스에서 생성 된 개체를 전달 하지 않아야 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0be1e-128">Because of this, callers should not pass objects that are created from this namespace at runtime to code that is not trusted.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
  </Docs>
</Namespace>