<Type Name="ImportCatalogPart" FullName="System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart">
  <Metadata>
    <Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="17bfe4fc2991ca45ffb31cad133a61b48da42cfa" />
    <Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="d31dc2ede16f6f7bc64e90d9f897ff54c4e3869b" />
    <Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="HT" />
    <Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="ko-KR" />
    <Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="04/03/2018" />
    <Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="30591097" />
  </Metadata>
  <TypeSignature Language="C#" Value="public sealed class ImportCatalogPart : System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart" />
  <TypeSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".class public auto ansi sealed beforefieldinit ImportCatalogPart extends System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart" />
  <TypeSignature Language="DocId" Value="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart" />
  <TypeSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public NotInheritable Class ImportCatalogPart&#xA;Inherits CatalogPart" />
  <TypeSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public ref class ImportCatalogPart sealed : System::Web::UI::WebControls::WebParts::CatalogPart" />
  <AssemblyInfo>
    <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
    <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
  </AssemblyInfo>
  <Base>
    <BaseTypeName>System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart</BaseTypeName>
  </Base>
  <Interfaces />
  <Docs>
    <summary>
      <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-101">
        <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> 컨트롤 또는 <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> 컨트롤로 사용되는 다른 ASP.NET 서버 컨트롤을 미리 정의된 설정으로 웹 페이지에 추가할 수 있도록 해당 컨트롤에 대한 설명 파일을 가져옵니다.</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="34ca0-101">Imports a description file for a <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> control (or other ASP.NET server control used as a <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> control), so that users can add the control to a Web page with pre-defined settings.</span>
      </span>
      <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-102">이 클래스는 상속될 수 없습니다.</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="34ca0-102">This class cannot be inherited.</span>
      </span>
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-103"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 컨트롤의 설정을 설명 하는 설명 파일을 가져오는 사용자가 사용 하면는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤 또는 사용자가을 추가 하는 서버 컨트롤을 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartZoneBase> 영역입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-103">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control enables users to import a description file that describes settings on a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control or server control that a user wants to add to a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartZoneBase> zone.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-104">설명 파일을 가져온 후의 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 파일에서 참조 하는 컨트롤 내에 표시는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 및 사용자 페이지에 컨트롤을 추가할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-104">After a user imports a description file, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control referenced in the file appears within the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, and a user can add the control to the page.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-105">Description 파일은 컨트롤 자체와 동일 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-105">The description file is not the same as the control itself.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-106">로 끝나는 XML 파일 인지는 합니다. 웹 파트 확장 주로 속성 값은 컨트롤의 상태를 설명 하는-이름/값 쌍을 포함 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-106">It is an XML file that ends with a .WebPart extension and contains name/value pairs--mostly property values--that describe the state of the control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-107">이 항목에 설명 된 대로 지정된 된 XML 형식에 따라 생성 되는 설명 파일 [웹 파트 컨트롤 설명 파일](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/480992e4-8fc7-43f8-bffc-ae97bbdfe5b8)합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-107">The description file is created according to a specified XML format, as described in the topic [Web Parts Control Description Files](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/480992e4-8fc7-43f8-bffc-ae97bbdfe5b8).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-108">Description 파일을 나타내는 컨트롤의 경우를 어셈블리로 컴파일할 수 있거나 또는.ascx 파일에 정의 된 사용자 정의 컨트롤 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-108">As for the control that the description file refers to, it can either be compiled into an assembly, or it can be a user control defined in an .ascx file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-109">두 경우 모두 가져온된 설명 파일에서 참조 된 컨트롤은 컨트롤을 시도 하는 페이지를 호스팅하는 웹 서버에 존재 해야 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-109">In either case, the control referenced in an imported description file must exist on the Web server that hosts the page that is attempting to import the control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-110">설명 파일에서 참조 하는 컨트롤을 포함 하는 컨트롤 이름 및 어셈블리 (또는 파일) 및 설명 파일에는 컨트롤의 속성 값, 모양 및 동작에 영향을 주는 설정이 포함 되어 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-110">The description file references the control name and the assembly (or file) that contains the control, and the description file contains settings that affect the control's property values, appearance, and behavior.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-111"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 컨트롤을 사용 하면 사용자가 컨트롤의 설정을 공유할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-111">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control enables users to share settings on controls.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-112">복잡 한 제어는 여러 속성 및 설정이 있을 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-112">A complex control can have many properties and settings.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-113">예를 들어 사용자 지정 큰 회사 내에서 일반적인 인트라넷 사이트의에서 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤에는 다양 한 데이터베이스 연결, 부서 정보 등 등 사용자의 환경에 고유한 값을 포함 하는 속성이 포함 될 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-113">For example, in a typical intranet site within a large company, a custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control might contain a number of properties that hold values specific to the users' environment, such as their database connections, departmental information, and so on.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-114">컨트롤의 모양에 영향을 주는 속성의 수를 포함할 수도 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-114">The control might also contain a number of properties that affect its appearance.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-115">한 명의 사용자 수 컨트롤 특정 사이트에 개인 설정 하 고 올바르게 작동, 컨트롤에 대 한 설명 파일 내보내고 나 다른 인트라넷에 완전히 구성 된 컨트롤을 추가할 파일을 가져올 수 있는 다른 사용자와 설명 파일을 공유 개인 설정에 허용 되는 사이트입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-115">One user could personalize the control on a particular site and get it working properly, export a description file for the control, and then share the description file with other users, who could import the file to add the fully configured control to other intranet sites that they are allowed to personalize.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-116">컴파일된 어셈블리 또는 컨트롤을 포함 하는 사용자 정의 컨트롤 파일 자신의 사이트를 호스팅하는 웹 서버에 존재 하 고, 사용자가 다른 웹 사이트에 컨트롤을 추가할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-116">As long as the compiled assembly or user control file containing the control exists on the Web server that is hosting their site, users can add the control to other Web sites.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-117">기준인 사용자 설명 파일을 가져올 (및 따라서 연결된 된 서버 컨트롤)를 웹 페이지에는 메커니즘은는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 컨트롤 페이지 개발자 웹 페이지에 추가 해야 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-117">The mechanism by which users import a description file (and hence its associated server control) into a Web page is the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, which a page developer must add to a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-118">사용자는 페이지 카탈로그 디스플레이 모드를 전환할 때는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 컨트롤이 표시 되 고, 사용자가이 컨트롤을 찾아 사용자 수는 있습니다. 웹 파트 설명 파일을 가져올 하려는 서버 컨트롤에 해당 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-118">When a user switches the page to catalog display mode, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control appears, and the user can user this control to browse to the .WebPart description file corresponding to the server control they want to import.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-119">UI 및에서 제공한 지침을 따라는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 컨트롤, 사용자가 원하는 서버 컨트롤 모양을 가져온된 설명 파일에 지정 된 대로 완전 하 게 구성 하는 속성이 있는 웹 페이지에 추가할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-119">Following the UI and instructions provided by the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, a user is able to add the desired server control into the Web page, with its appearance and properties fully configured as specified in the imported description file.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-120">전에 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤의 설명 파일을 가져올 수, 사용자는 먼저 (내보내기) 만들어야 파일에서 기존 기반 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-120">Before a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control's description file can be imported, a user must first create (export) the file based on an existing <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-121">다음 조건이 충족 될 경우 컨트롤에 대 한 설명 파일을 내보낼 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-121">A description file can be exported for a control if the following conditions are met:</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-122">컨트롤으로 표시 된 속성에는 `Personalizable` 특성입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-122">The control has properties marked with the `Personalizable` attribute.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-123">Web.config 파일에는 `enableExport` 특성 값으로 설정 `true` 에 `<webParts>` 요소입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-123">The Web.config file has the `enableExport` attribute value set to `true` on the `<webParts>` element.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-124">값을 설정 하는 개발자는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart.ExportMode%2A> 속성의 기본값 이외의 값으로 컨트롤을 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartExportMode.None>, 내보내기를 금지 하 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-124">A developer sets the value of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart.ExportMode%2A> property on the control to a value other than the default value of <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartExportMode.None>, which prohibits export.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-125">경우는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart.ExportMode%2A> 속성 값으로 설정 됩니다 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartExportMode.NonSensitiveData>, 포함 된 속성은 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PersonalizableAttribute.IsSensitive%2A> 인 매개 변수는 `Personalizable` 특성 사용자 설명 파일을 내보낼 때 내보내집니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-125">If the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart.ExportMode%2A> property value is set to <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartExportMode.NonSensitiveData>, any property that contains an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PersonalizableAttribute.IsSensitive%2A> parameter with a `Personalizable` attribute is not exported when a user exports a description file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-126">따라서 특정 한 상황에서 내보내지 연결 문자열과 같은 중요 한 데이터를 방지 하기 위해 컨트롤 개발자가 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-126">This enables control developers to prevent sensitive data, such as connection strings, from being exported in certain situations.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-127">사용자가 저장 하는 지침을 수행 하는 컨트롤의 동사 메뉴에 표시 되는 내보내기 동사를 클릭 하 여 내보내기에 대해 설정 된 컨트롤을 내보낼 수는 있습니다. 컨트롤에 대 한 웹 파트 설명 파일입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-127">A user can export a control that has been enabled for export by clicking the export verb that appears in the verbs menu of the control, and following the instructions to save a .WebPart description file for the control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-128">그런 다음 다른 사용자가 컨트롤의 고유 인스턴스를 구성 하려면이 파일을 가져올 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-128">Other users can then import this file to configure their own instances of the control.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-129"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 클래스 여러 속성을 포함 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-129">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class contains several properties.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-130"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> 속성을 설명 파일을 찾을 때 사용자에 대 한 지침이 포함 된 텍스트를 포함 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-130">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> property contains text with instructions for users when they browse to locate the description file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-131"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> 속성 내에 표시 되는 가져온된 컨트롤에 대 한 레이블로 사용 되는 텍스트가 포함 된 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-131">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> property contains text that serves as a label for the imported control as it appears within the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-132"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> 컨트롤 설명을 가져올 때 오류가 발생 하는 경우 표시 되는 텍스트를 포함 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-132">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> contains text that is displayed if an error occurs when a control description is being imported.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-133"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> 속성에 대 한 기본 제목을 할당을 기본 속성을 재정의 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 개발자 제목을 할당 하지 않는 경우를 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-133">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> property overrides the base property to assign a default title for an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control if the developer does not assign a title.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-134"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> 클릭할 설명 파일을 업로드 하는 단추에 대 한 텍스트를 포함 하는 속성 및 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> 속성 업로드 프로세스에 대 한 지침이 포함 되어 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-134">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> property contains the text for the button that the user clicks to upload the description file, and the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> property contains the instructions for the upload process.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-135"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 클래스도 몇 가지 고유한 메서드를 포함 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-135">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class also contains several unique methods.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-136"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> 메서드에서 검색은 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> 각각에 대 한 개체 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤 수 있도록 하는 카탈로그에는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 컨트롤을 해당 형식의 인스턴스를 만들 필요 없이 각 서버 컨트롤에 대 한 정보를 표시 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-136">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method retrieves a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object for each <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control in the catalog, which enables an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control to display information about each server control without having to create an instance of it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-137"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> 메서드는 특정 인스턴스를 가져옵니다 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 메서드에 전달 된 설명에 따라 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-137">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method gets an instance of a particular <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control, based on the description passed to the method.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-138">사용과 관련 된 몇 가지 내재 된 위험을 가지는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-138">There are some inherent risks associated with using the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-139">한 가지 예는 악성 데이터를 가져오는 데 사용 되는 설명 파일을 통해 웹 응용 프로그램에 가져오는 가능성이 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-139">One example is the possibility of importing malicious data into your Web application through the description files used for importing.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-140">배치한 경우 악성 스크립트 코드 설명 파일에 문자열 속성의 값으로, 다음 해당 스크립트가 수 잠재적으로 실행 될 사용자 설명 파일을 가져옵니다를 웹 페이지에 참조 된 서버 컨트롤을 추가 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-140">If someone has placed malicious script code as the value of a string property in the description file, then that script could potentially be executed when a user imports the description file and adds the referenced server control to a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-141">악성 데이터와 함께 설명 파일을 가져올 위험을 최소화 하려면 문자열 형식의 속성이 있는 서버 컨트롤 항상 인코딩해야 속성 데이터 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-141">To minimize the risk of importing description files with malicious data, server controls that have string-typed properties should always encode the property data.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-142">형식 설명 파일을 통해 가져오는 경우에 또 다른 위험 (참조 [웹 파트 컨트롤 설명 파일](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/480992e4-8fc7-43f8-bffc-ae97bbdfe5b8)).</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-142">Another risk involves importing types through description files (see [Web Parts Control Description Files](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/480992e4-8fc7-43f8-bffc-ae97bbdfe5b8)).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-143">악의적인 사용자는 많은 어셈블리를 로드 하는 요청을 전송할 수는 <xref:System.AppDomain>때문에 메모리 사용량이 지나치게 많은 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-143">A malicious user could submit requests to load many assemblies into the <xref:System.AppDomain>, resulting in an excessive amount of memory being consumed.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-144">가져오기와 관련 된 위험을 방지 하려면 기능을 해제 하면는 완전히 가져오기 기능을 사용 하지 않고 또는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-144">To avoid the risks associated with import, you can disable the feature altogether by not using the import feature or the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-145">또는 컨트롤에 액세스할 수 있는 사용자를 제한할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-145">Or you can limit what users have access to the control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-146">그렇게 할 수 프로그래밍 방식으로 역할 관리를 사용 하 여 (참조 [권한 부여를 사용 하 여 역할 관리](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/01954ce4-39a2-487f-8153-a69f6f6f3195)).</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-146">You could do this programmatically, using role management (see [Managing Authorization Using Roles](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/01954ce4-39a2-487f-8153-a69f6f6f3195)).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-147">예를 들어, 페이지를 로드 하는 경우 사용자가 관리자 역할 등 특정 역할에 있는지 여부를 테스트할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-147">For instance, when the page loads, you could test to see whether a user is in a certain role, such as the administrator role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-148">경우 역할에 사용자가을 프로그래밍 방식으로 추가할 수는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 컨트롤을 해당 사용자에 대 한 페이지입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-148">If the user is in the role, you could programmatically add the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control to the page for that user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-149">사용할 수 있는 사용자 집합을 제한 하는 선언적 접근 방식을 사용할 수도 있습니다는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-149">You could also use a declarative approach to limit the set of users that can use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span>  <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-150">카탈로그가 포함 된 웹 페이지 내에서 두 개의 넣을 수 있습니다 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> 컨트롤: 가져올 수 있는 사용자 및 사용자에 게 없습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-150">Within your web page that contains a catalog, you could place two <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> controls: one for users who can import, and one for those who cannot.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-151">가져올 수 있는 사용자에 대 한 영역에는 포함 된 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-151">The zone for users who can import would contain the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-152">영역 자체 내에 저장할 수는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.LoginView> 사용자 또는 역할 지정 하는 인증 된 것만 시간대에 있는 컨트롤의 사용을 제한 하는 데 사용할 수 있는 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-152">The zone itself could be placed inside of a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.LoginView> control, which would enable you to limit use of the control in the zone to only those authenticated users or roles that you specify.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-153">다음 코드 예제에서는 사용 하는 방법을 보여 줍니다.는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 웹 페이지에 선언적으로 또는 프로그래밍 방식으로 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-153">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control declaratively and programmatically on a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-154">예제는 네 부분으로 이루어져 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-154">The example has four parts:</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-155">웹 파트 페이지에서 디스플레이 모드를 변경할 수 있게 해 주는 사용자 정의 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-155">A user control that enables you to change display modes on a Web Parts page.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-156">포함 하는 웹 페이지는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> 제어 및 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-156">A Web page that contains a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> control and an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-157">두 개의 사용자 지정을 포함 하는 소스 코드 파일 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-157">A source code file that contains two custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-158">브라우저에서 페이지를 로드 하는 경우이 예제에서는 작동 하는 방식에 대해 설명 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-158">An explanation of how the example works when you load the page in a browser.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-159">이 코드 예제는 첫 번째 부분에는 사용자가 웹 페이지에 대 한 디스플레이 모드를 변경할 수 있는 사용자 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-159">The first part of this code example is the user control that enables users to change display modes on a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-160">다음 소스 코드 파일에 배치 하 고 Displaymodemenucs.ascx 또는 (언어에 따라 사용 하는) Displaymodemenuvb.ascx 이름을 해야 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-160">You should place the following source code in a file and name it Displaymodemenucs.ascx or Displaymodemenuvb.ascx (depending on which language you are using).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-161">이 컨트롤의 모드 및 소스 코드에 대 한 설명을 표시 하는 대 한 세부 정보를 참조 [연습: 웹 파트 페이지에](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/24e42f74-82dc-4c13-8574-130398985fc0)합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-161">For details about display modes and a description of the source code in this control, see [Walkthrough: Changing Display Modes on a Web Parts Page](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/24e42f74-82dc-4c13-8574-130398985fc0).</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#7](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/DisplayModeMenuCS.ascx#7)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#7](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/DisplayModeMenuVB.ascx#7)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-162">코드 예제에서는 두 번째 부분에는 웹 페이지입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-162">The second part of the code example is the Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-163">페이지의 위쪽에는 두 `register` 지시문, 사용자 정의 컨트롤 및 두 개의 사용자 지정을 포함 하는 컴파일된 구성 요소에 대 한 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-163">At the top of the page are two `register` directives, one for the user control and one for the compiled component that contains the two custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-164">페이지에 대 한 선언적 참조에는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 선언적 요소의 적절 한 계층 구조 내에 중첩 된 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-164">Notice that the page has a declarative reference to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, nested within the proper hierarchy of declarative elements.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-165">몇 가지 속성 값에서 선언적으로 할당 된도 확인할 수는 `<asp:importcatalogpart>` 요소입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-165">Notice also that several property values are assigned declaratively on the `<asp:importcatalogpart>` element.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-166">또한는 `Button1_Click` 에 다양 한 속성 값을 업데이트 하는 메서드는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-166">Also, the `Button1_Click` method updates a number of property values on the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-167">페이지의 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartZone> 제어, 두 개의 사용자 지정 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤도 선언 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-167">In the page's <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartZone> control, the two custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls are declared.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-168">`<aspSample:userinfowebpart>` 컨트롤에는 `exportmode="all"` 특성이 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-168">The `<aspSample:userinfowebpart>` control has an `exportmode="all"` attribute on it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-169">이 특성은 사용자가 다른 사용자가 가져오기 description 파일을 사용 하 여 컨트롤을 가져올 수 있는 컨트롤에 대 한 설명 파일을 내보낼 수 있도록 해야 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-169">This attribute is required to enable users to export a description file for the control, which can then be imported by other users who wish to import the control using the description file.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-170">설명 파일을 내보낼 웹 파트 응용 프로그램의 사용자가 사용할 수 있도록 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤에도 추가 하 여 웹 응용 프로그램에서 내보내기 기능을 활성화 해야는 `enableExport="true"` 특성을 `<webParts>` 요소 (의 의자식인`<system.web>`요소)의 Web.config 파일에 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-170">To enable users of a Web Parts application to export a description file for <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls, you must also enable the export feature in the Web application by adding an `enableExport="true"` attribute to the `<webParts>` element (which is a child of the `<system.web>` element) in the Web.config file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-171">내보내기는 기본적으로 비활성화 되어, 응용 프로그램에 대 한 내보내기를 아직 설정 하지 않은 경우 Web.config 파일을 편집한 지금 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-171">Export is disabled by default, so if you have not yet enabled export for your application, edit the Web.config file and do it now.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#1](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#1)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#1](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#1)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-172">코드 예제에서는 세 번째 부분은 두에 대 한 소스 코드 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-172">The third part of the code example is the source code for the two <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-173">이러한 컨트롤의 일부 속성으로 표시 된 통지는 `WebBrowsable` 특성입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-173">Notice that some properties on these controls are marked with the `WebBrowsable` attribute.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-174">이 통해는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PropertyGridEditorPart> 컨트롤을 동적으로 컨트롤이 편집 모드일 때 해당 속성을 편집 하는 사용자에 대 한 사용자 인터페이스 (UI)를 생성 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-174">This enables the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PropertyGridEditorPart> control to dynamically generate the user interface (UI) for a user to edit those properties when the controls are in edit mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-175">속성 또한 서식이 지정 된는 `WebDisplayName` 특성 편집 UI의 각 컨트롤 옆에 표시 되는 레이블 텍스트를 지정 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-175">The properties are also marked with a `WebDisplayName` attribute, to specify the text of the label that appears next to each control in the editing UI.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-176">코드 예제를 실행 하려면이 소스 코드를 컴파일해야 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-176">For the code example to run, you must compile this source code.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-177">명시적으로 컴파일할 수 있으며 결과 어셈블리를 웹 사이트의 Bin 폴더 또는 전역 어셈블리 캐시에 넣을 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-177">You can compile it explicitly and put the resulting assembly in your Web site's Bin folder or the global assembly cache.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-178">또는 여기서 것 동적으로 컴파일되는 런타임 시 사이트의 App_Code 폴더에 소스 코드를 넣을 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-178">Alternatively, you can put the source code in your site's App_Code folder, where it will be dynamically compiled at run time.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-179">이 코드 예제는 동적 컴파일과 사용합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-179">This code example uses dynamic compilation.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-180">두 컴파일 방법을 보여 주는 연습을 참조 [연습: 개발 및 사용자 지정 웹 서버 컨트롤을 사용 하 여](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6d90782a-a1a4-45a6-b2d4-cf6362b83b08)합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-180">For a walkthrough that demonstrates both methods of compiling, see [Walkthrough: Developing and Using a Custom Web Server Control](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6d90782a-a1a4-45a6-b2d4-cf6362b83b08).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-181">사용자 지정 컨트롤 `TextDisplayWebPart` 사용 하 여 웹 페이지에서 참조 되는 `<aspSample:TextDisplayWebPart>` 요소입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-181">The custom control called `TextDisplayWebPart` is referenced on the Web page with an `<aspSample:TextDisplayWebPart>` element.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-182">다른 컨트롤을 호출 `UserInfoWebPart`도 선언 됩니다 웹 페이지에 처음에 경우에 컨트롤에 대 한 설명 파일을 가져올 수 있는 기능을 설명 하기 위해 나중에 제거 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-182">The other control, called `UserInfoWebPart`, is also declared on the Web page initially, though you will remove it later to demonstrate the ability to import a description file for a control.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#6](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/userinfowebpart.cs#6)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#6](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/userinfowebpart.vb#6)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-183">이제이 코드 예제를 실행 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-183">Now run the code example.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-184">브라우저에서 웹 페이지를 로드 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-184">Load the Web page in a browser.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-185">편집 하는 첫 번째 단계는 `UserInfoWebPart` 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-185">The first step is to edit the `UserInfoWebPart` control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-186">사용 하 여는 **디스플레이 모드** 드롭 다운 목록 컨트롤 및 선택 **편집** 페이지 편집 모드를 전환 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-186">Use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control and select **Edit** to switch the page to edit mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-187">동사 메뉴의 클릭는 `UserInfoWebPart` (제목 표시줄의 아래쪽 화살표)를 제어 하 고 클릭 한 다음 **편집**합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-187">Click the verbs menu of the `UserInfoWebPart` control (the downward arrow in the title bar), and then click **Edit**.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-188">아래에 몇 가지 편집 컨트롤이 표시 편집 UI가 나타나면는 `UserInfoWebPart` 필드 값을 편집 하는 데 사용할 수 있는 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-188">When the editing UI appears, several editing controls appear below the `UserInfoWebPart` control that you can use to edit its field values.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-189">일부 필드를 편집을 클릭 **확인**를 사용 하 여는 **디스플레이 모드** 드롭 다운 페이지 찾아보기 모드를 되돌립니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-189">Edit some fields, click **OK**, and then use the **Display Mode** drop-down to return the page to browse mode.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-190">두 번째 단계는 내보내기는 합니다. 에 대 한 웹 파트 설명 파일은 `UserInfoWebPart` 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-190">The second step is to export a .WebPart description file for the `UserInfoWebPart` control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-191">동사 메뉴 사용자 지정 컨트롤 (제목 표시줄의 아래쪽 화살표로 표시 됨)를 클릭 하 고 클릭 **내보내기**합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-191">Click the verbs menu on the custom control (represented by the downward arrow in the title bar), and click **Export**.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-192">지침에 따라 저장을 합니다. 컨트롤에 대 한 웹 파트 설명 파일입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-192">Follow the instructions to save a .WebPart description file for the control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-193">이제 웹 페이지를 닫고 편집기에서 페이지 소스를 편집 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-193">Now close the Web page, and edit the page source in an editor.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-194">삭제 된 `<aspSample:userinfowebpart>` 컨트롤 선언 요소를 저장 하 고 파일을 닫습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-194">Delete the `<aspSample:userinfowebpart>` control declaration element, then save and close the file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-195">(아직 없는 사용자를 시뮬레이션 하기 위해이 작업을 수행 하는 `UserInfoWebPart` 제어 페이지에 컨트롤을 가져올 수 있습니다).</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-195">(You are doing this step to simulate a user who does not yet have the `UserInfoWebPart` control, so you can import the control to the page).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-196">브라우저에서 다시 웹 페이지를 로드 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-196">Load the Web page again in a browser.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-197">`UserInfoWebPart` 컨트롤 나타나지 않고 제거 했기 때문에 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-197">The `UserInfoWebPart` control should not appear, because you removed it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-198">사용 하 여는 **디스플레이 모드** 드롭 다운 목록 컨트롤 및 선택 **카탈로그** 페이지 카탈로그 모드로 전환할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-198">Use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control and select **Catalog** to switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-199">에 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 컨트롤을 클릭는 **찾아보기** 을 찾아서 단추는 합니다. 웹 파트 파일을 만든 다음 클릭는 **업로드** 단추입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-199">In the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, click the **Browse** button, and browse to the .WebPart file you created, then click the **Upload** button.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-200">컨트롤에 대 한 참조는 옆에 확인란이 표시 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-200">A reference to the control should appear with a check box next to it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-201">확인란을 선택한 다음 클릭 **추가** 를 페이지에 컨트롤을 추가 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-201">Select the check box, then click **Add** to add the control to the page.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-202">이 페이지의이 보기에 있는 동안 클릭는 **업데이트 ImportCatalogPart** 에 다양 한 속성 값을 업데이트 하는 프로그래밍 방식으로 영향을 보려면 페이지의 맨 아래에 있는 단추는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-202">While you are in this view of the page, click the **Update ImportCatalogPart** button near the bottom of the page to see the effect of programmatically updating a number of property values on the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-203">단추를 클릭 한 후 UI의 다양 한 속성이 변경 되는 방법을 확인 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-203">After clicking the button, observe how the various properties are changed in the UI.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-204">마지막으로, 클릭 **닫기** 모드를 종료 하 카탈로그 찾아보기 모드로 페이지를 반환 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-204">Finally, click **Close** to exit catalog mode and return the page to browse mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-205">`UserInfoWebPart` 이전 내보낸 때 값이 포함 된 컨트롤의 페이지에 표시 되어야 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-205">The `UserInfoWebPart` control should now appear in the page, containing the values that it had when you exported it earlier.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
    <altmember cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PageCatalogPart" />
    <altmember cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart" />
  </Docs>
  <Members>
    <Member MemberName=".ctor">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public ImportCatalogPart ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig specialname rtspecialname instance void .ctor() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.#ctor" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Sub New ()" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; ImportCatalogPart();" />
      <MemberType>Constructor</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-206">
            <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart" /> 클래스의 새 인스턴스를 초기화합니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-206">Initializes a new instance of the <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart" /> class.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-207"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.%23ctor%2A> 에 선언 된 생성자가 없습니다; 생성자는 기본은 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 클래스 및 따라서 특별 작업 수행 되는 클래스의 새 인스턴스를 만들 때.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-207">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.%23ctor%2A> constructor is a default; no constructor is declared in the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class and hence no special tasks are carried out when a new instance of the class is created.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-208">.NET Framework 클래스의 인스턴스를 만드는 생성자를 내부적으로 사용 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-208">The .NET Framework uses the constructor internally to create an instance of the class.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-209">일반적으로 사용 하도록 않아도 됩니다는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.%23ctor%2A> 사용자 코드에서 프로그래밍 방식으로 생성자입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-209">Normally you will not need to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.%23ctor%2A> constructor programmatically in your own code.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-210">페이지 개발자가 디자인 타임에 선언적으로 페이지에 추가할 수는 컨트롤의 의도 한 사용 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-210">The intended use of the control is for page developers to add it to a page declaratively at design time.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="BrowseHelpText">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public string BrowseHelpText { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string BrowseHelpText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Property BrowseHelpText As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; property System::String ^ BrowseHelpText { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-211">사용자가 설명 파일의 위치를 찾을 때 지침을 제공하는 텍스트 메시지를 가져오거나 설정합니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-211">Gets or sets a text message that instructs users to browse to the location of a description file.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-212">메시지 텍스트가 포함된 문자열입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-212">A string that contains the text of the message.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-213">기본값은 .NET Framework에서 제공하는 culture별 메시지입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-213">The default value is a culture-specific message supplied by the .NET Framework.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-214"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> 속성은 사용자 가장 먼저 가져온된 컨트롤을 추가 하 고 작업을 수행 해야에 대 한 간단한 개요: 경로 입력 하거나 파일을 탐색 하 여 설명 파일의 위치를 제공 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-214">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> property gives users a simple overview of the first thing they must do in the process of adding an imported control: provide the location of a description file, by either typing in a path or browsing to the file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-215">이 속성에 대 한 사용자 지정 값을 제공 하는 이유는을 설명 파일을 찾기 위해 이동 해야 하는 특정 네트워크 공유 등의 사용자에 대 한 특별 지침이 있는 경우.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-215">A typical reason to supply a custom value for this property is if you have special instructions for users, such as a specific network share to which they should browse to locate a description file.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-216">다음 코드 예제에서는 사용 하는 방법을 보여 줍니다.는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> 속성 선언적 방법과 프로그래밍 방식으로 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-216">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> property declaratively and programmatically.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-217">전체 코드 및 예제를 실행 하는 데 필요한 지침의 예 섹션을 참조는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 클래스 개요입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-217">For the full code and instructions required to run the example, see the Example section of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class overview.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-218">다음 코드 섹션에서는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> 속성 값이 컨트롤에 대 한 선언적으로 설정 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-218">In the following section of code, notice that the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> property value is set declaratively for the control.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#2)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#2)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-219">코드의이 섹션에는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> 프로그래밍 방식으로 속성 값이 할당 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-219">In this section of code, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> property value is assigned programmatically.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#3)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#3)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-220">브라우저에서 페이지를 로드할 때 사용할 수 있습니다는 **디스플레이 모드** 선택 하려면 드롭다운 목록 컨트롤 **카탈로그 모드** 카탈로그 모드로 전환 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-220">When you load the page in a browser, you can use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control to select **Catalog Mode** and switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-221">카탈로그 모드와 설명 파일 업로드 페이지와 사용자 인터페이스 (UI)에 표시 되는 다양 한 텍스트 문자열에 대 한 참고는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-221">With the page in catalog mode and the description file uploaded, note the various text strings displayed in the user interface (UI) for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-222">클릭는 **설명 파일 업로드** 단추를 일부의 UI의 속성에 대 한 텍스트에 대 한 텍스트를 포함 하 여 변경 되는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> 속성입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-222">If you click the **Upload Description File** button, the text for several of the properties in the UI is changed, including the text for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> property.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="CreateChildControls">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="protected internal override void CreateChildControls ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method familyorassemblyhidebysig virtual instance void CreateChildControls() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.CreateChildControls" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Protected Friend Overrides Sub CreateChildControls ()" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="protected public:&#xA; override void CreateChildControls();" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Void</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary>To be added.</summary>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="DefaultButton">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public override string DefaultButton { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string DefaultButton" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.DefaultButton" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Overrides Property DefaultButton As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; virtual property System::String ^ DefaultButton { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Attributes>
        <Attribute>
          <AttributeName>System.ComponentModel.Browsable(false)</AttributeName>
        </Attribute>
        <Attribute>
          <AttributeName>System.ComponentModel.EditorBrowsable(System.ComponentModel.EditorBrowsableState.Never)</AttributeName>
        </Attribute>
        <Attribute>
          <AttributeName>System.Web.UI.Themeable(false)</AttributeName>
        </Attribute>
      </Attributes>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-223">단추가 포함된 폼이 렌더링될 때 포커스를 받는 기본 단추로 처리되는 UI(사용자 인터페이스)의 단추를 가져오거나 설정합니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-223">Gets or sets what button in the user interface (UI) is treated as the default button that receives the focus when form that contains the button is rendered.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-224">이 속성은 페이지 개발자 코드에서는 호출할 수 없습니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-224">This property is not intended to be called from page developer code.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-225">
            <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button" /> 컨트롤에서 기본 포커스를 받는 <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel" />의 ID가 포함된 문자열입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-225">A string that contains the ID of the <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button" /> that receives the default focus in a <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel" /> control.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-226">이 속성에 대 한 코드에서 상속 되며, 기본 속성을 재정의 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel> 클래스 디자이너에서 속성을 숨기고 테마 영향을 주지 않도록 방지 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-226">The code for this property overrides the base property inherited from the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel> class to hide the property from designers and prevent it from being affected by themes.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-227">Public 인 경우에이 웹 파트 컨트롤 집합이 컨트롤의 기본 렌더링을 위해 내부적으로 사용 됩니다 속성과 페이지 개발자가 사용할 수 없습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-227">Though it is public, this property is used internally by the Web Parts control set for default rendering of this control and is not intended to be used by page developers.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-228">이 속성은 테마 또는 스타일시트 테마에 의해 설정될 수 없습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-228">This property cannot be set by themes or style sheet themes.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-229">자세한 내용은 참조 <xref:System.Web.UI.ThemeableAttribute> 및 [ASP.NET 테마와 스킨](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/5df3ebbd-d46c-4502-9406-02f9df4ef2c3)합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-229">For more information, see <xref:System.Web.UI.ThemeableAttribute> and [ASP.NET Themes and Skins](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/5df3ebbd-d46c-4502-9406-02f9df4ef2c3).</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <altmember cref="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel.DefaultButton" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public override System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig virtual instance class System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Overrides Function GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions () As WebPartDescriptionCollection" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; override System::Web::UI::WebControls::WebParts::WebPartDescriptionCollection ^ GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions();" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-230">카탈로그에서 사용할 수 있는 <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> 컨트롤에 대한 설명의 컬렉션을 반환합니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-230">Returns a collection of descriptions of the available <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> controls in a catalog.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-231">카탈로그의 각 컨트롤에 대한 <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection" />이 들어 있는 <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription" />입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-231">A <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection" /> that contains a <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription" /> for each control in a catalog.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-232"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> 에 선언 된 추상 기본 메서드에 대 한 구현을 제공 하는 메서드는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> 클래스입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-232">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method provides an implementation for the abstract base method declared in the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> class.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-233"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> 메서드 카탈로그의 각 컨트롤에 대 한 설명 정보를 반환 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-233">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method returns description information for each control in a catalog.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-234">경우에 한 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 하 고, 있을 수 있습니다 하나만 서버 컨트롤 카탈로그에 한 번에 있지만 컨트롤이 여러 개 있는 경우 메서드가 실행 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-234">Note that in the case of an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, there can be only one server control in the catalog at a time, even though the method would work if there were multiple controls.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-235">A <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> 개체는 개체에 대 한 중요 한 정보를 포함 하는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤과에서 상속 하는 몇 가지 중요 한 속성의 값에 대 한 개체 참조를 해당 ID를 포함 하 여 컨트롤의 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part> 클래스 같은 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> 및 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Description%2A>합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-235">A <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object is an object that contains essential information about a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control, including its ID, an object reference to the control, and the values of several important properties that are inherited from the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part> class, such as <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> and <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Description%2A>.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-236"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> 메서드는 성능을 향상 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-236">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method improves performance.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-237">에 포함 된 제목, 설명, 아이콘 (있는 경우) 및 ID를 포함 하 여 각 컨트롤에 대 한 정보는 카탈로그를 만들 때 필요한</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-237">When a catalog is created, it needs some information about each control it contains, including a title, a description, an icon (if one exists), and an ID.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-238">이 정보를 얻으려면 각 컨트롤의 인스턴스를 만드는 것이 아니라는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> 영역 호출 카탈로그를 생성 하는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> 메서드와 호출만의 인스턴스가 아닌 컨트롤에 대 한 설명 정보를 반환 합니다.는 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-238">Rather than having to create an instance of each control to get this information, a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> zone that creates a catalog calls the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method, and the call returns only the description information for the control rather than an instance of the control.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-239">다음 코드 예제에서는 사용 하는 방법을 보여 줍니다.는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> 웹 페이지에는 메서드.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-239">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method on a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-240">예제는 네 부분으로 이루어져 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-240">The example has four parts:</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-241">웹 파트 페이지에서 디스플레이 모드를 변경할 수 있게 해 주는 사용자 정의 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-241">A user control that enables you to change display modes on a Web Parts page.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-242">포함 하는 웹 페이지는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> 제어 및 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 컨트롤을 사용 하는 코드가 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> 메서드.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-242">A Web page that contains a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> control and an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, along with code that uses the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-243">두 개의 사용자 지정을 포함 하는 소스 코드 파일 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-243">A source code file that contains two custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-244">브라우저에서 페이지를 로드 하는 경우이 예제에서는 작동 하는 방식에 대해 설명 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-244">An explanation of how the example works when you load the page in a browser.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-245">이 코드 예제는 첫 번째 부분에는 사용자가 웹 페이지에 대 한 디스플레이 모드를 변경할 수 있는 사용자 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-245">The first part of this code example is the user control that enables users to change display modes on a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-246">다음 소스 코드 파일에 배치 하 고 Displaymodemenucs.ascx 또는 (언어에 따라 사용 하는) Displaymodemenuvb.ascx 이름을 해야 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-246">You should place the following source code in a file and name it Displaymodemenucs.ascx or Displaymodemenuvb.ascx (depending on which language you are using).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-247">이 컨트롤의 모드 및 소스 코드에 대 한 설명을 표시 하는 대 한 세부 정보를 참조 [연습: 웹 파트 페이지에](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/24e42f74-82dc-4c13-8574-130398985fc0)합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-247">For details about display modes and a description of the source code in this control, see [Walkthrough: Changing Display Modes on a Web Parts Page](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/24e42f74-82dc-4c13-8574-130398985fc0).</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#7](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/CS/DisplayModeMenuCS.ascx#7)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#7](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/VB/DisplayModeMenuVB.ascx#7)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-248">코드 예제에서는 두 번째 부분에는 웹 페이지입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-248">The second part of the code example is the Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-249">페이지의 위쪽에는 두 `register` 지시문, 사용자 정의 컨트롤 및 두 개의 사용자 지정을 포함 하는 컴파일된 구성 요소에 대 한 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-249">At the top of the page are two `register` directives, one for the user control and one for the compiled component that contains the two custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-250">이러한 두 컨트롤은 페이지의 태그에서 선언적으로 참조 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-250">Both of these controls are referenced declaratively in the markup of the page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-251">에 대 한 선언적 참조에는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤 (둘 다로 시작는 `aspSample` 접두사), 각는 `exportMode="all"` 특성이 추가 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-251">On the declarative references to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls (both begin with an `aspSample` prefix), note that each has an `exportMode="all"` attribute added to it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-252">이 특성을 사용 하면 내보낼 수는 있습니다. 웹 파트 페이지에 컨트롤을 가져오려는 단계를 나중에 사용할 수 있는 컨트롤에 대 한 설명 파일입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-252">This attribute enables you to export a .WebPart description file for the control, which you will use in a later to step to import the control to a page.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-253">설명 파일을 내보낼 웹 파트 응용 프로그램의 사용자가 사용할 수 있도록 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤에도 추가 하 여 웹 응용 프로그램에서 내보내기 기능을 활성화 해야는 `enableExport="true"` 특성을 `<webParts>` 요소 (의 의자식인`<system.web>`요소)의 Web.config 파일에 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-253">To enable users of a Web Parts application to export a description file for <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls, you must also enable the export feature in the Web application by adding an `enableExport="true"` attribute to the `<webParts>` element (which is a child of the `<system.web>` element) in the Web.config file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-254">내보내기는 기본적으로 비활성화 되어, 응용 프로그램에 대 한 내보내기를 아직 설정 하지 않은 경우 Web.config 파일을 편집한 지금 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-254">Export is disabled by default, so if you have not yet enabled export for your application, edit the Web.config file and do it now.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-255">웹 페이지에 대 한 선언적 참조에는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 선언적 요소의 적절 한 계층 구조 내에 중첩 된 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-255">The Web page also has a declarative reference to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, nested within the proper hierarchy of declarative elements.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-256"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> 에 대 한 코드 내 메서드가 호출 되는 `Button1_Click` 메서드.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-256">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method is called within the code for the `Button1_Click` method.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#1](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/CS/ImportCatalogPart_GetCS.aspx#1)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#1](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/VB/ImportCatalogPart_GetVB.aspx#1)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-257">코드 예제에서는 세 번째 부분은 두에 대 한 소스 코드 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-257">The third part of the code example is the source code for the two <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-258">코드 예제를 실행 하려면이 소스 코드를 컴파일해야 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-258">For the code example to run, you must compile this source code.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-259">명시적으로 컴파일할 수 있으며 결과 어셈블리를 웹 사이트의 Bin 폴더 또는 전역 어셈블리 캐시에 넣을 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-259">You can compile it explicitly and put the resulting assembly in your Web site's Bin folder or the global assembly cache.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-260">또는 여기서 것 동적으로 컴파일되는 런타임 시 사이트의 App_Code 폴더에 소스 코드를 넣을 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-260">Alternatively, you can put the source code in your site's App_Code folder, where it will be dynamically compiled at run time.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-261">이 코드 예제는 동적 컴파일과 사용합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-261">This code example uses dynamic compilation.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-262">두 컴파일 방법을 보여 주는 연습을 참조 [연습: 개발 및 사용자 지정 웹 서버 컨트롤을 사용 하 여](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6d90782a-a1a4-45a6-b2d4-cf6362b83b08)합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-262">For a walkthrough that demonstrates both methods of compiling, see [Walkthrough: Developing and Using a Custom Web Server Control](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6d90782a-a1a4-45a6-b2d4-cf6362b83b08).</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#6](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/CS/userinfowebpart.cs#6)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#6](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/VB/userinfowebpart.vb#6)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-263">이제이 코드 예제를 실행 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-263">Now run the code example.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-264">브라우저에서 웹 페이지를 로드 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-264">Load the Web page in a browser.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-265">첫 번째 단계는 내보내기는 합니다. 각 웹 파트 설명 파일 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤 (에 대 한는 `TextDisplayWebPart` 및에 대 한는 `UserInfoWebPart` 컨트롤).</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-265">The first step is export a .WebPart description file for each <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control (for the `TextDisplayWebPart` and for the `UserInfoWebPart` control).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-266">각 컨트롤에 대 한 동사 메뉴 컨트롤 (제목 표시줄의 아래쪽 화살표로 표시 됨)를 클릭 하 고 클릭 **내보내기**합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-266">For each control, click the verbs menu on the control (represented by the downward arrow in the title bar), and click **Export**.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-267">지침에 따라 저장을 합니다. 컨트롤에 대 한 웹 파트 설명 파일입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-267">Follow the instructions to save a .WebPart description file for the control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-268">각 컨트롤에 대 한 설명 파일을 내보낸 후 웹 페이지를 닫고 편집기에서 페이지 소스를 편집 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-268">After you have exported a description file for each control, close the Web page, and edit the page source in an editor.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-269">삭제 된 `<aspSample:userinfowebpart>` 및 `<aspSample:textdisplaywebpart>` 제어 선언 요소, 그런 다음 저장 하 고 파일을 닫습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-269">Delete the `<aspSample:userinfowebpart>` and the `<aspSample:textdisplaywebpart>` control declaration elements, then save and close the file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-270">(아직 없는 이러한 컨트롤을 페이지에 컨트롤을 가져올 수 있도록 사용자를 시뮬레이션 하기 위해이 작업을 수행 하려는).</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-270">(You are doing this step to simulate a user who does not yet have these controls, so you can import the controls to the page).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-271">브라우저에서 다시 웹 페이지를 로드 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-271">Load the Web page again in a browser.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-272">사용 하 여는 **디스플레이 모드** 드롭 다운 목록 컨트롤 및 선택 **카탈로그** 페이지 카탈로그 모드로 전환할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-272">Use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control and select **Catalog** to switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-273">에 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 컨트롤을 클릭는 **찾아보기** 단추로 이동 된 합니다. 웹 파트 파일을 찾아 하나를 선택한 다음 클릭는 **업로드** 단추입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-273">In the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, click the **Browse** button, browse to the .WebPart files you created, select one, then click the **Upload** button.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-274">컨트롤에 대 한 참조는 옆에 확인란이 표시 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-274">A reference to the control should appear with a check box next to it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-275">확인란을 선택한 다음 클릭 **추가** 를 페이지에 컨트롤을 추가 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-275">Select the check box, then click **Add** to add the control to the page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-276">다른 컨트롤에 대 한이 프로세스를 반복 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-276">Repeat this process for the other control.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-277">이 페이지의이 보기에 있는 동안 클릭는 **Get WebPart Description** 프로그래밍 방식으로 액세스의 영향을 보려면 페이지의 맨 아래에 있는 단추는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> 제어 설명에 현재 로드 된 개체는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-277">While you are in this view of the page, click the **Get WebPart Description** button near the bottom of the page to see the effect of programmatically accessing the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object for the control description currently loaded in the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-278">에 있는 설명 정보에 액세스 하는 데 사용 하는 메서드가 `Button1_Click` 페이지 소스 방법이 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> 메서드.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-278">The method used to access the description details, found in the `Button1_Click` method of the page source, is the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-279">단추 아래 레이블 컨트롤에 대 한 기본적인 정보를 표시합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-279">A label below the button displays basic details about the control.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-280">첫 번째 컨트롤을 추가한 후 페이지에 두 번째 컨트롤을 추가 하는 프로세스를 반복 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-280">After adding the first control, repeat the process to add the second control to the page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-281">마지막으로, 클릭 **닫기** 모드를 종료 하 카탈로그 찾아보기 모드로 페이지를 반환 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-281">Finally, click **Close** to exit catalog mode and return the page to browse mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-282">이제 두 사용자 지정 컨트롤 이전 설명 파일을 내보낼 때가지고 있던 값이 포함 된 페이지에 나타납니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-282">Both custom controls should now appear in the page, containing the values they had when you exported description files earlier.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <altmember cref="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart(System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription)" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="GetWebPart">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public override System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart GetWebPart (System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription description);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig virtual instance class System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart GetWebPart(class System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription description) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart(System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Overrides Function GetWebPart (description As WebPartDescription) As WebPart" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; override System::Web::UI::WebControls::WebParts::WebPart ^ GetWebPart(System::Web::UI::WebControls::WebParts::WebPartDescription ^ description);" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="description" Type="System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="description">
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-283">컨트롤에 대한 세부 정보가 들어 있는 <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription" />입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-283">A <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription" /> that contains details about the control.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-284">메서드에 전달된 설명의 값을 기준으로 <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> 컨트롤에 대한 참조를 반환합니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-284">Returns a reference to a <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> control based on the values in the description passed into the method.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-285">설명이 <paramref name="description" />의 값과 일치하는 <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> 컨트롤입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-285">A <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> control whose description matches the values in <paramref name="description" />.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-286"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> 메서드 반환에 대 한 참조는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 설명 세부 정보가의 값과 일치 하는 컨트롤은 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> 메서드에 전달 된 개체입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-286">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method returns a reference to a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control whose description details match the values of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object passed into the method.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-287">와 함께이 메서드는 일반적으로 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> 메서드를 카탈로그에 있는 컨트롤의 설명을 검색 하는 데 사용 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-287">Typically, this method is used together with the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method, which is used to retrieve the descriptions of controls in the catalog.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-288">개별 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤을 검색 하거나 개별 전달 하 여 필요에 따라 조작한 다음 수 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> 개체는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> 메서드.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-288">Individual <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls can then be retrieved or manipulated as needed by passing individual <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> objects to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-289">다음 코드 예제에서는 사용 하는 방법을 보여 줍니다.는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> 웹 페이지에는 메서드.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-289">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method on a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-290">예제는 네 부분으로 이루어져 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-290">The example has four parts:</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-291">웹 파트 페이지에서 디스플레이 모드를 변경할 수 있게 해 주는 사용자 정의 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-291">A user control that enables you to change display modes on a Web Parts page.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-292">포함 하는 웹 페이지는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> 제어 및 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 컨트롤을 사용 하는 코드가 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> 메서드.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-292">A Web page that contains a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> control and an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, along with code that uses the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-293">두 개의 사용자 지정을 포함 하는 소스 코드 파일 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-293">A source code file that contains two custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-294">브라우저에서 페이지를 로드 하는 경우이 예제에서는 작동 하는 방식에 대해 설명 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-294">An explanation of how the example works when you load the page in a browser.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-295">이 코드 예제는 첫 번째 부분에는 사용자가 웹 페이지에 대 한 디스플레이 모드를 변경할 수 있는 사용자 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-295">The first part of this code example is the user control that enables users to change display modes on a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-296">다음 소스 코드 파일에 배치 하 고 Displaymodemenucs.ascx 또는 (언어에 따라 사용 하는) Displaymodemenuvb.ascx 이름을 해야 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-296">You should place the following source code in a file and name it Displaymodemenucs.ascx or Displaymodemenuvb.ascx (depending on which language you are using).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-297">이 컨트롤의 모드 및 소스 코드에 대 한 설명을 표시 하는 대 한 세부 정보를 참조 [연습: 웹 파트 페이지에](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/24e42f74-82dc-4c13-8574-130398985fc0)합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-297">For details about display modes and a description of the source code in this control, see [Walkthrough: Changing Display Modes on a Web Parts Page](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/24e42f74-82dc-4c13-8574-130398985fc0).</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#7](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/CS/DisplayModeMenuCS.ascx#7)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#7](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/VB/DisplayModeMenuVB.ascx#7)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-298">코드 예제에서는 두 번째 부분에는 웹 페이지입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-298">The second part of the code example is the Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-299">페이지의 위쪽에는 두 `register` 지시문, 사용자 정의 컨트롤 및 두 개의 사용자 지정을 포함 하는 컴파일된 구성 요소에 대 한 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-299">At the top of the page are two `register` directives, one for the user control and one for the compiled component that contains the two custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-300">이러한 두 컨트롤은 페이지의 태그에서 선언적으로 참조 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-300">Both of these controls are referenced declaratively in the markup of the page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-301">에 대 한 선언적 참조에는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤 (둘 다로 시작는 `aspSample` 접두사), 각는 `exportMode="all"` 특성이 추가 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-301">On the declarative references to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls (both begin with an `aspSample` prefix), note that each has an `exportMode="all"` attribute added to it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-302">이 특성을 사용 하면 내보낼 수는 있습니다. 웹 파트 페이지에 컨트롤을 가져오려는 단계를 나중에 사용할 수 있는 컨트롤에 대 한 설명 파일입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-302">This attribute enables you to export a .WebPart description file for the control, which you will use in a later to step to import the control to a page.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-303">설명 파일을 내보낼 웹 파트 응용 프로그램의 사용자가 사용할 수 있도록 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤에도 추가 하 여 웹 응용 프로그램에서 내보내기 기능을 활성화 해야는 `enableExport="true"` 특성을 `<webParts>` 요소 (의 의자식인`<system.web>`요소)의 Web.config 파일에 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-303">To enable users of a Web Parts application to export a description file for <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls, you must also enable the export feature in the Web application by adding an `enableExport="true"` attribute to the `<webParts>` element (which is a child of the `<system.web>` element) in the Web.config file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-304">내보내기는 기본적으로 비활성화 되어, 응용 프로그램에 대 한 내보내기를 아직 설정 하지 않은 경우 Web.config 파일을 편집한 지금 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-304">Export is disabled by default, so if you have not yet enabled export for your application, edit the Web.config file and do it now.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-305">웹 페이지에 대 한 선언적 참조에는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 선언적 요소의 적절 한 계층 구조 내에 중첩 된 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-305">The Web page also has a declarative reference to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, nested within the proper hierarchy of declarative elements.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-306"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> 에 대 한 코드 내 메서드가 호출 되는 `Button2_Click` 메서드.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-306">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method is called within the code for the `Button2_Click` method.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#1](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/CS/ImportCatalogPart_GetCS.aspx#1)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#1](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/VB/ImportCatalogPart_GetVB.aspx#1)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-307">코드 예제에서는 세 번째 부분은 두에 대 한 소스 코드 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-307">The third part of the code example is the source code for the two <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-308">코드 예제를 실행 하려면이 소스 코드를 컴파일해야 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-308">For the code example to run, you must compile this source code.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-309">명시적으로 컴파일할 수 있으며 결과 어셈블리를 웹 사이트의 Bin 폴더 또는 전역 어셈블리 캐시에 넣을 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-309">You can compile it explicitly and put the resulting assembly in your Web site's Bin folder or the global assembly cache.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-310">또는 여기서 것 동적으로 컴파일되는 런타임 시 사이트의 App_Code 폴더에 소스 코드를 넣을 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-310">Alternatively, you can put the source code in your site's App_Code folder, where it will be dynamically compiled at run time.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-311">이 코드 예제는 동적 컴파일과 사용합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-311">This code example uses dynamic compilation.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-312">두 컴파일 방법을 보여 주는 연습을 참조 [연습: 개발 및 사용자 지정 웹 서버 컨트롤을 사용 하 여](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6d90782a-a1a4-45a6-b2d4-cf6362b83b08)합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-312">For a walkthrough that demonstrates both methods of compiling, see [Walkthrough: Developing and Using a Custom Web Server Control](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6d90782a-a1a4-45a6-b2d4-cf6362b83b08).</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#6](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/CS/userinfowebpart.cs#6)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#6](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/VB/userinfowebpart.vb#6)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-313">이제이 코드 예제를 실행 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-313">Now run the code example.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-314">브라우저에서 웹 페이지를 로드 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-314">Load the Web page in a browser.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-315">첫 번째 단계는 내보내기는 합니다. 각 웹 파트 설명 파일 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤 (에 대 한는 `TextDisplayWebPart` 및에 대 한는 `UserInfoWebPart` 컨트롤).</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-315">The first step is export a .WebPart description file for each <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control (for the `TextDisplayWebPart` and for the `UserInfoWebPart` control).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-316">각 컨트롤에 대 한 동사 메뉴 컨트롤 (제목 표시줄의 아래쪽 화살표로 표시 됨)를 클릭 하 고 클릭 **내보내기**합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-316">For each control, click the verbs menu on the control (represented by the downward arrow in the title bar), and click **Export**.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-317">지침에 따라 저장을 합니다. 컨트롤에 대 한 웹 파트 설명 파일입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-317">Follow the instructions to save a .WebPart description file for the control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-318">각 컨트롤에 대 한 설명 파일을 내보낸 후 웹 페이지를 닫고 편집기에서 페이지 소스를 편집 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-318">After you have exported a description file for each control, close the Web page, and edit the page source in an editor.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-319">삭제 된 `<aspSample:userinfowebpart>` 및 `<aspSample:textdisplaywebpart>` 제어 선언 요소, 그런 다음 저장 하 고 파일을 닫습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-319">Delete the `<aspSample:userinfowebpart>` and the `<aspSample:textdisplaywebpart>` control declaration elements, then save and close the file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-320">(아직 없는 이러한 컨트롤을 페이지에 컨트롤을 가져올 수 있도록 사용자를 시뮬레이션 하기 위해이 작업을 수행 하려는).</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-320">(You are doing this step to simulate a user who does not yet have these controls, so you can import the controls to the page).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-321">브라우저에서 다시 웹 페이지를 로드 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-321">Load the Web page again in a browser.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-322">사용 하 여는 **디스플레이 모드** 드롭 다운 목록 컨트롤 및 선택 **카탈로그** 페이지 카탈로그 모드로 전환할 수 있습니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-322">Use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control and select **Catalog** to switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-323">에 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 컨트롤을 클릭는 **찾아보기** 단추로 이동 된 합니다. 웹 파트 파일을 찾아 하나를 선택한 다음 클릭는 **업로드** 단추입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-323">In the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, click the **Browse** button, browse to the .WebPart files you created, select one, then click the **Upload** button.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-324">컨트롤에 대 한 참조는 옆에 확인란이 표시 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-324">A reference to the control should appear with a check box next to it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-325">제어 설명에 업로드 했으므로 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 컨트롤을 클릭는 **사용 GetWebPart** 페이지의 아래쪽에 있는 단추입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-325">Now that the control description is uploaded to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, click the **Use GetWebPart** button near the bottom of the page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-326">이 호출의 효과 설명 합니다는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> 메서드와에 현재 로드 된 컨트롤 설명을 전달는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-326">This will demonstrate the effect of calling the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method and passing to it the control description currently loaded in the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-327">된 연결 된 서버 컨트롤은 즉시 추가 웹 페이지에 사용자가 클릭 하지는 **추가** 단추입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-327">Note that the associated server control is added immediately to the Web page, without the user having to click the **Add** button.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-328"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> 호출 되는 메서드는 `Button2_Click` 페이지 소스의 메서드는 반환는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤에 로드 된 현재 설명과 연결 된는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-328">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method, which is called in the `Button2_Click` method of the page source, returns the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control associated with the current description that is loaded in the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-329">다음은 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager.AddWebPart%2A> 메서드가 호출 되 고 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> 컨트롤이 페이지에 직접 추가 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-329">Next the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager.AddWebPart%2A> method is called, and the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control is directly added to the page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-330">여기에서는에서 프로그래밍 방식으로 컨트롤을 추가 하는 방법을 보여 줍니다.는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 사용자 개입 없이 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-330">This demonstrates how to add a control programmatically from the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control without user intervention.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-331">첫 번째 컨트롤을 추가한 후 페이지에 두 번째 컨트롤을 추가 하는 프로세스를 반복 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-331">After adding the first control, repeat the process to add the second control to the page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-332">마지막으로, 클릭 **닫기** 모드를 종료 하 카탈로그 찾아보기 모드로 페이지를 반환 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-332">Finally, click **Close** to exit catalog mode and return the page to browse mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-333">이제 두 사용자 지정 컨트롤 이전 설명 파일을 내보낼 때가지고 있던 값이 포함 된 페이지에 나타납니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-333">Both custom controls should now appear in the page, containing the values they had when you exported description files earlier.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-334">
            <paramref name="description" />가 <see langword="null" />인 경우</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-334">
              <paramref name="description" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-335">
            <paramref name="description" />이 사용할 수 있는 <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription" /> 값이 아닌 경우</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-335">
              <paramref name="description" /> is not an available <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription" /> value.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <altmember cref="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="ImportedPartLabelText">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public string ImportedPartLabelText { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string ImportedPartLabelText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Property ImportedPartLabelText As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; property System::String ^ ImportedPartLabelText { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-336">가져온 컨트롤의 카탈로그 내에 있는 컨트롤을 나타내거나 설명하는 파일을 가져온 후에 표시되는 텍스트를 가져오거나 설정합니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-336">Gets or sets text displayed after a user imports a description file to represent or describe the imported control within the catalog of imported controls.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-337">레이블 텍스트가 포함된 문자열입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-337">A string that contains the text of the label.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-338">기본값은 .NET Framework에서 제공하는 culture별 메시지입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-338">The default value is a culture-specific message supplied by the .NET Framework.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-339"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> 속성에 포함 된 컨트롤을 설명 하는 일반, 짧은 레이블이 데 일반적으로 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-339">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> property is typically used to contain a short, general label that describes the control contained in the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-340">다음 코드 예제에서는 사용 하는 방법을 보여 줍니다.는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> 속성 선언적 방법과 프로그래밍 방식으로 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-340">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> property declaratively and programmatically.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-341">전체 코드 및 예제를 실행 하는 데 필요한 지침의 예 섹션을 참조는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 클래스 개요입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-341">For the full code and instructions required to run the example, see the Example section of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class overview.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-342">다음 코드 섹션에서는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> 속성 값이 컨트롤에 대 한 선언적으로 설정 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-342">In the following section of code, notice that the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> property value is set declaratively for the control.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#2)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#2)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-343">코드의이 섹션에는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> 프로그래밍 방식으로 속성 값이 할당 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-343">In this section of code, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> property value is assigned programmatically.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#3)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#3)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-344">브라우저에서 페이지를 로드할 때 사용할 수 있습니다는 **디스플레이 모드** 선택 하려면 드롭다운 목록 컨트롤 **카탈로그 모드** 카탈로그 모드로 전환 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-344">When you load the page in a browser, you can use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control to select **Catalog Mode** and switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-345">카탈로그 모드와 설명 파일 업로드 페이지와 사용자 인터페이스 (UI)에 표시 되는 다양 한 텍스트 문자열에 대 한 참고는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-345">With the page in catalog mode and the description file uploaded, note the various text strings displayed in the user interface (UI) for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-346">클릭는 **설명 파일 업로드** 단추를 일부의 UI의 속성에 대 한 텍스트에 대 한 텍스트를 포함 하 여 변경 되는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> 속성입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-346">If you click the **Upload Description File** button, the text for several of the properties in the UI is changed, including the text for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> property.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="LoadControlState">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="protected internal override void LoadControlState (object savedState);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method familyorassemblyhidebysig virtual instance void LoadControlState(object savedState) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.LoadControlState(System.Object)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Protected Friend Overrides Sub LoadControlState (savedState As Object)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="protected public:&#xA; override void LoadControlState(System::Object ^ savedState);" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Void</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="savedState" Type="System.Object" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="savedState">To be added.</param>
        <summary>To be added.</summary>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="OnInit">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="protected internal override void OnInit (EventArgs e);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method familyorassemblyhidebysig virtual instance void OnInit(class System.EventArgs e) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.OnInit(System.EventArgs)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Protected Friend Overrides Sub OnInit (e As EventArgs)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="protected public:&#xA; override void OnInit(EventArgs ^ e);" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Void</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="e" Type="System.EventArgs" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="e">To be added.</param>
        <summary>To be added.</summary>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="PartImportErrorLabelText">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public string PartImportErrorLabelText { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string PartImportErrorLabelText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Property PartImportErrorLabelText As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; property System::String ^ PartImportErrorLabelText { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-347">가져오는 중 오류가 발생할 경우 표시되는 오류 메시지를 가져오거나 설정합니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-347">Gets or sets an error message that is displayed if an error occurs during the import process.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-348">레이블 텍스트가 포함된 문자열입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-348">A string that contains the text of the label.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-349">기본값은 .NET Framework에서 제공하는 culture별 메시지입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-349">The default value is a culture-specific message supplied by the .NET Framework.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-350"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> 속성은 일부 문제 또는 오류 페이지 설명 파일을 가져오려고 시도 하는 동안 발생 하는 경우 사용자에 게 알리는 데 유용 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-350">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> property is useful for notifying a user if some problem or error occurs while the page attempts to import a description file.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-351">다음 코드 예제에서는 사용 하는 방법을 보여 줍니다.는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> 속성 선언적 방법과 프로그래밍 방식으로 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-351">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> property declaratively and programmatically.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-352">전체 코드 및 예제를 실행 하는 데 필요한 지침의 예 섹션을 참조는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 클래스 개요입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-352">For the full code and instructions required to run the example, see the Example section of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class overview.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-353">다음 코드 섹션에서는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> 속성 값이 컨트롤에 대 한 선언적으로 설정 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-353">In the following section of code, notice that the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> property value is set declaratively for the control.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#2)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#2)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-354">코드의이 섹션에는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> 프로그래밍 방식으로 속성 값이 할당 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-354">In this section of code, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> property value is assigned programmatically.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#3)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#3)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-355">브라우저에서 페이지를 로드할 때 사용할 수 있습니다는 **디스플레이 모드** 선택 하려면 드롭다운 목록 컨트롤 **카탈로그 모드** 카탈로그 모드로 전환 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-355">When you load the page in a browser, you can use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control to select **Catalog Mode** and switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-356">카탈로그 모드와 설명 파일 업로드 페이지와 사용자 인터페이스 (UI)에 표시 되는 다양 한 텍스트 문자열에 대 한 참고는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-356">With the page in catalog mode and the description file uploaded, note the various text strings displayed in the user interface (UI) for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-357">클릭는 **설명 파일 업로드** 단추를 일부의 UI의 속성에 대 한 텍스트에 대 한 텍스트를 포함 하 여 변경 되는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> 속성입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-357">If you click the **Upload Description File** button, the text for several of the properties in the UI is changed, including the text for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> property.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="Render">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="protected internal override void Render (System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter writer);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method familyorassemblyhidebysig virtual instance void Render(class System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter writer) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Render(System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Protected Friend Overrides Sub Render (writer As HtmlTextWriter)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="protected public:&#xA; override void Render(System::Web::UI::HtmlTextWriter ^ writer);" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Void</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="writer" Type="System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="writer">To be added.</param>
        <summary>To be added.</summary>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="RenderContents">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="protected internal override void RenderContents (System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter writer);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method familyorassemblyhidebysig virtual instance void RenderContents(class System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter writer) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.RenderContents(System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Protected Friend Overrides Sub RenderContents (writer As HtmlTextWriter)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="protected public:&#xA; override void RenderContents(System::Web::UI::HtmlTextWriter ^ writer);" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Void</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="writer" Type="System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="writer">To be added.</param>
        <summary>To be added.</summary>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="SaveControlState">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="protected internal override object SaveControlState ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method familyorassemblyhidebysig virtual instance object SaveControlState() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.SaveControlState" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Protected Friend Overrides Function SaveControlState () As Object" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="protected public:&#xA; override System::Object ^ SaveControlState();" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Object</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary>To be added.</summary>
        <returns>To be added.</returns>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="Title">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public override string Title { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string Title" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Overrides Property Title As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; virtual property System::String ^ Title { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-358">
            <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart" /> 컨트롤의 제목 표시줄에 나타나는 제목을 가져오거나 설정합니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-358">Gets or sets the title that appears in the title bar of an <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart" /> control.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-359">컨트롤의 제목으로 사용되는 문자열입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-359">A string that is used as the title of the control.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-360">기본값은 웹 파트 컨트롤 집합에서 제공하는 계산된 컨트롤 이름입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-360">The default value is a calculated control name supplied by the Web Parts control set.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-361"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> 속성 값의 제목 표시줄에 표시 됩니다는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 카탈로그 모드에서 표시 된 경우를 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-361">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> property value is displayed in the title bar of an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control when the control is visible in catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-362">페이지에 컨트롤을 선언한 때 사용 하 여 속성에 대 한 값을 설정할 수 있습니다는 `Title` 특성입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-362">When the control is declared in a page, you can set a value for the property by using the `Title` attribute.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-363">제목에 대 한 값을 지정 하지 않는 경우 culture 별 기본 값이이 컨트롤에서 사용자가을 편집할 수 있는 속성의 종류를 설명 하기 위해 사용 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-363">If you do not supply a value for the title, a culture-specific default value is used to describe the kind of properties that this control allows users to edit.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-364">다음 코드 예제에서는 사용 하는 방법을 보여 줍니다.는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> 속성 선언적 방법과 프로그래밍 방식으로 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-364">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> property declaratively and programmatically.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-365">전체 코드 및 예제를 실행 하는 데 필요한 지침의 예 섹션을 참조는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 클래스 개요입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-365">For the full code and instructions required to run the example, see the Example section of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class overview.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-366">다음 코드 섹션에서는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> 속성 값이 컨트롤에 대 한 선언적으로 설정 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-366">In the following section of code, notice that the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> property value is set declaratively for the control.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#2)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#2)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-367">코드의이 섹션에는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> 프로그래밍 방식으로 속성 값이 할당 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-367">In this section of code, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> property value is assigned programmatically.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#3)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#3)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-368">브라우저에서 페이지를 로드할 때 사용할 수 있습니다는 **디스플레이 모드** 선택 하려면 드롭다운 목록 컨트롤 **카탈로그 모드** 카탈로그 모드로 전환 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-368">When you load the page in a browser, you can use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control to select **Catalog Mode** and switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-369">카탈로그 모드와 설명 파일 업로드 페이지와 사용자 인터페이스 (UI)에 표시 되는 다양 한 텍스트 문자열에 대 한 참고는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-369">With the page in catalog mode and the description file uploaded, note the various text strings displayed in the user interface (UI) for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-370">클릭는 **설명 파일 업로드** 단추를 일부의 UI의 속성에 대 한 텍스트에 대 한 텍스트를 포함 하 여 변경 되는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> 속성입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-370">If you click the **Upload Description File** button, the text for several of the properties in the UI is changed, including the text for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> property.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="UploadButtonText">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public string UploadButtonText { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string UploadButtonText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Property UploadButtonText As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; property System::String ^ UploadButtonText { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-371">설명 파일의 업로드를 초기화하는 <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button" /> 컨트롤의 텍스트를 가져오거나 설정합니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-371">Gets or sets the text for the <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button" /> control that initiates the upload of a description file.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-372">
            <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button" />의 텍스트로 사용되는 문자열입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-372">A string that is used as the text for a <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button" />.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-373">기본값은 웹 파트 컨트롤 집합에서 제공하는 culture별 문자열입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-373">The default value is a culture-specific string supplied by the Web Parts control set.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-374"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> 속성에 대 한 텍스트를 제공는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button> 업로드 프로세스를 시작 하는 컨트롤입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-374">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> property provides the text for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button> control that initiates the upload process.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-375">이 속성 또는에 사용자 지정 텍스트를 할당 하는 경우는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> 속성 텍스트 지우기 사용자 설명 파일 업로드 하 고 있는지 확인 해야 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-375">If you assign custom text to this property, or to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> property, the text should make clear that the user is uploading a description file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-376">텍스트 하지 말 하거나 업로드 프로세스 컨트롤 자체을 업로드 하 고 실제로 의미 해야 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-376">The text should not say or imply that the upload process is actually uploading the control itself.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-377">다음 코드 예제에서는 사용 하는 방법을 보여 줍니다.는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> 속성 선언적 방법과 프로그래밍 방식으로 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-377">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> property declaratively and programmatically.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-378">전체 코드 및 예제를 실행 하는 데 필요한 지침의 예 섹션을 참조는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 클래스 개요입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-378">For the full code and instructions required to run the example, see the Example section of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class overview.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-379">다음 코드 섹션에서는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> 속성 값이 컨트롤에 대 한 선언적으로 설정 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-379">In the following section of code, notice that the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> property value is set declaratively for the control.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#2)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#2)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-380">코드의이 섹션에는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> 프로그래밍 방식으로 속성 값이 할당 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-380">In this section of code, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> property value is assigned programmatically.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#3)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#3)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-381">브라우저에서 페이지를 로드할 때 사용할 수 있습니다는 **디스플레이 모드** 선택 하려면 드롭다운 목록 컨트롤 **카탈로그 모드** 카탈로그 모드로 전환 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-381">When you load the page in a browser, you can use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control to select **Catalog Mode** and switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-382">카탈로그 모드와 설명 파일 업로드 페이지와 사용자 인터페이스 (UI)에 표시 되는 다양 한 텍스트 문자열에 대 한 참고는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-382">With the page in catalog mode and the description file uploaded, note the various text strings displayed in the user interface (UI) for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-383">클릭는 **설명 파일 업로드** 단추를 일부의 UI의 속성에 대 한 텍스트에 대 한 텍스트를 포함 하 여 변경 되는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> 속성입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-383">If you click the **Upload Description File** button, the text for several of the properties in the UI is changed, including the text for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> property.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="UploadHelpText">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public string UploadHelpText { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string UploadHelpText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Property UploadHelpText As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; property System::String ^ UploadHelpText { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-384">사용자에게 설명 파일의 업로드 방법을 알려 주는 메시지 텍스트를 가져오거나 설정합니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-384">Gets or sets the text of the message that tells the user how to upload a description file.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-385">사용자에게 설명 파일을 업로드하는 방법을 알려 주는 데 사용되는 문자열입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-385">A string that is used as instructions for the user to upload a description file.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-386">기본값은 웹 파트 컨트롤 집합에서 제공하는 culture별 문자열입니다.</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="34ca0-386">The default value is a culture-specific string supplied by the Web Parts control set.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-387"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> 속성은 간략 한 문장이 나 구를 인하 설명 파일을 업로드 하는 단추를 클릭 하 여 사용자에 대 한 지침을 제공 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-387">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> property provides a brief sentence or phrase of instructions for users, telling them to click a button to upload the description file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-388">이 속성 또는에 사용자 지정 텍스트를 할당 하는 경우는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> 속성 텍스트 지우기 사용자 설명 파일 업로드 하 고 있는지 확인 해야 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-388">If you assign custom text to this property, or to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> property, the text should make clear that the user is uploading a description file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-389">텍스트 하지 말 하거나 업로드 프로세스 컨트롤 자체을 업로드 하 고 실제로 의미 해야 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-389">The text should not say or imply that the upload process is actually uploading the control itself.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-390">다음 코드 예제에서는 사용 하는 방법을 보여 줍니다.는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> 속성 선언적 방법과 프로그래밍 방식으로 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-390">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> property declaratively and programmatically.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-391">전체 코드 및 예제를 실행 하는 데 필요한 지침의 예 섹션을 참조는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 클래스 개요입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-391">For the full code and instructions required to run the example, see the Example section of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class overview.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-392">다음 코드 섹션에서는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> 속성 값이 컨트롤에 대 한 선언적으로 설정 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-392">In the following section of code, notice that the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> property value is set declaratively for the control.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#2)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#2)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-393">코드의이 섹션에는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> 프로그래밍 방식으로 속성 값이 할당 됩니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-393">In this section of code, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> property value is assigned programmatically.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#3)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#3)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-394">브라우저에서 페이지를 로드할 때 사용할 수 있습니다는 **디스플레이 모드** 선택 하려면 드롭다운 목록 컨트롤 **카탈로그 모드** 카탈로그 모드로 전환 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-394">When you load the page in a browser, you can use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control to select **Catalog Mode** and switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-395">카탈로그 모드와 설명 파일 업로드 페이지와 사용자 인터페이스 (UI)에 표시 되는 다양 한 텍스트 문자열에 대 한 참고는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> 제어 합니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-395">With the page in catalog mode and the description file uploaded, note the various text strings displayed in the user interface (UI) for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="34ca0-396">클릭는 **설명 파일 업로드** 단추를 일부의 UI의 속성에 대 한 텍스트에 대 한 텍스트를 포함 하 여 변경 되는 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> 속성입니다.</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="34ca0-396">If you click the **Upload Description File** button, the text for several of the properties in the UI is changed, including the text for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> property.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
  </Members>
</Type>